<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <faction.tsm>T.S.M</faction.tsm>
  <faction.tsm.description>The Teamwork Secrecy Mercyn Company has gradually evolved into a significant faction. With its wide-reaching influence and resources, the company's role has expanded beyond mere commercial operations, extending into the political and military realms of the deep-sea world, forming a powerful faction with a profound impact on deep-sea exploration and regional security.</faction.tsm.description>
  <faction.tsm.shortdescription>TSM is an outstanding multi-field enterprise. The company is renowned for its exceptional escort services, providing unparalleled safety guarantees, ensuring the safety of deep-sea explorers and merchant vessels.</faction.tsm.shortdescription>
  <randomnews35>A new submarine is clearing threats from the waters of Europa. The Coalition has responded positively and hopes more teams will join in to make the channels safer.</randomnews35>
  <randomnews36>TSM has your back</randomnews36>
  <locationchange.tsm_city.changeto.abandoned>TSM's fortress city [previousname] has fallen.</locationchange.tsm_city.changeto.abandoned>
  <locationchange.tsm_city.changeto.none>TSM's fortress city [previousname] has relocated to a more suitable location.</locationchange.tsm_city.changeto.none>
  <locationchange.none.changeto.tsm_city>TSM discovered the ecological zone [previousname] and established a fortress city there.</locationchange.none.changeto.tsm_city>
  <locationchange.abandoned.changeto.tsm_city>TSM cleared the internal threats of [previousname] and established a city on this foundation.</locationchange.abandoned.changeto.tsm_city>
  <!--过关文书-->
  <eventtext.unlockpathgeneric.nomoney.tsm>“If you're not capable and not planning to pay the deposit, don't waste my precious nap time.”</eventtext.unlockpathgeneric.nomoney.tsm>
  <eventtext.unlockpath.refusebribe.tsm>Thought better of it</eventtext.unlockpath.refusebribe.tsm>
  <lockedpathtooltiptsmreputation>This passage has been sealed off by TSM. If you want to continue, your reputation with ‖color:faction.tsm‖ TSM must exceed [requiredreputation], and you must obtain the administrator's permission. You can view your current reputation in the info interface.\n\nCurrent Reputation: [currentreputation]</lockedpathtooltiptsmreputation>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmc1>“You want to pass this checkpoint?”\nThe administrator looked up, his gaze sweeping through the fleet via the control panel's light screen, then skillfully operating the terminal,\n“Wait a moment, I need to verify your fleet's records.”\nA few seconds later\n“Welcome, Captain. After review, your reputation is sufficient. Permission to travel to the Europan Ridge has been granted. The authorization has been synced to your terminal.”\nHe paused, a hint of seriousness flashing in his eyes\n“But, the Europan Ridge is far more perilous than previous routes. Deep-sea currents, unknown creatures, and wrecked ships may threaten your safety at any moment. Captain, please stay calm and cautious.”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmc2>“You want to dive into deeper waters?”\nThe administrator smiled faintly, lightly touching the terminal, “Hold on a moment, I need to pull up your records.”\nA few seconds later, the data on the screen made the administrator frown, “Sorry, according to the current records, you haven't met the requirements to pass the blockade.”\n“But...” he paused, glancing from the terminal to you, with a slightly playful tone, “This is T.S.M, after all. In these waters, there are always exceptions. If you insist on heading deeper, we can make an exception—provided you pay a 2000mk deposit.”\nThe administrator leaned back in his chair, his gaze filled with a mix of anticipation and calculation, “Now, the decision is yours. What will you choose?”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmc2>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1>2000MK, deal!</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1.tsmc1>“Great! I like people with this kind of attitude. I'll let the folks at the blockade know; you just go ahead.”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1.nomoney>“No money? Well, then I can't help you. Your fleet's records don't look too promising. If you're broke, consider earning some cash through bounties.”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo1.nomoney>
  <eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo2.tsmc1>“If you're not capable and not planning to pay the deposit, don't waste my precious rest time.”</eventtext.unlockpathcoldcaverns.tsmo2.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmc1>“You want to head to the Aphotic Plateau?”\n“Please hold on a second,” the administrator's fingers swiftly glided over the terminal.\nA moment later, the administrator smiled in satisfaction, “It seems you've been contributing a lot to the Ice Ridge. I'm pleased to announce—you now have access to the Aphotic Plateau.”\n“May you sail smoothly in those dark depths. Safe travels, Captain.”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmc2>“You want to enter the Aphotic Plateau?”\nThe administrator squinted, lightly tapping the terminal, and chuckled softly after a moment, “Judging by the records, this doesn't look too promising…”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmc2>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1>“I understand, I understand, is 4500mk enough?”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1.tsmc1>“Your records aren't bad, but are you truly ready? This dangerous sea won't accept just anyone.”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1.nomoney>“Not enough money, huh? Well, we've recently posted some bounty missions, why not give them a shot?”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo1.nomoney>
  <eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo2.tsmc1>“Whether you go or not, that's not for us to decide, it's up to you. After all, the Europa Ridge is a great place to live, isn't it?”</eventtext.unlockpatheuropanridge.tsmo2.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmc1>“Ah, it's you! You're the star fleet everyone's been talking about, right? Your tales are all over Europa.”\n“Of course, of course, this means you've earned the right to traverse the Aphotic Plateau. You may now set sail for the Great Sea. Not many fleets have managed to make it there under the current circumstances.”\nThe administrator stood up and shook your hand, “I'll notify the checkpoint ahead to allow your passage into the Abyss. May you proceed safely through those unfathomable waters.”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmc2>“My apologies,”\nThe administrator sighed, a hint of helplessness in his expression, “I know it hasn't been easy for you to make it this far, you've overcome many obstacles. But we cannot risk letting an unqualified fleet venture into the Great Sea.”\nHe looked up, his tone softening slightly, “This is for your protection. I hope you understand, not everyone can handle the dangers lurking there.”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmc2>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1>“What if we pay a 9K deposit?”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1.tsmc1>“According to our regulations, you can indeed pass,” he said slowly, his tone solemn.\n“But I must advise you to think carefully. The Great Sea is not a place to tread lightly.” He gazed at you, his voice low and full of meaning.\n“That sea holds endless unknowns and dangers, and not everyone returns from it. Please consider carefully.”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1.nomoney>“If you don't have enough money, don't push it. Besides, money isn't everything—stay alive first, then talk.”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo1.nomoney>
  <eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo2.tsmc1>“As I said, there's no need to go overboard. The Aphotic Plateau are great, livable, and TSM's headquarters are there. Why not buy an apartment and retire?”</eventtext.unlockpathaphoticplateau.tsmo2.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmc1>The administrator saw you from afar and stood up, shaking your hand. “Look who it is! The famous star fleet! What can I do for you this time?”\nUpon hearing your request to travel to the Hydrothermal Wastes, the administrator's expression stiffened slightly. He was silent for a moment, then spoke in a slow, deliberate tone: “The number of creatures in the next area is abnormally high, and the currents stirred by geothermal activity will make navigation even more dangerous.” He looked at you, as if gauging your resolve. “Are you truly prepared?”\nHe straightened up and saluted you. “Then, please be careful—do not be careless.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmc2>“So you want to enter the Hydrothermal Wasteland? Many fleets have tried, and many have gone missing. This is T.S.M's deposit system. If you're determined to go, take a look.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmc2>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1>“17000mk? No problem, I'll transfer the money shortly.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1.tsmc1>“Don't rush. You can always reconsider. It's rare to see someone who's both earning money with their life and buying their way into danger. First time I've seen someone paying to die.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1.tsmc1>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1.nomoney>“Then don't go. You need both money and life to enjoy it. As long as you're alive, you'll always have money.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo1.nomoney>
  <eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo2.tsmc1>“Many could've stood where you are now, with the courage to press forward.”</eventtext.unlockpathgreatsea.tsmo2.tsmc1>
  <!--站点事件对话-->
  <!--降临派裴拉文-->
  <tsm.a8>Hey, dude, welcome to our outpost. We've been having some trouble lately, can I ask you a favor?</tsm.a8>
  <tsm.a81>Though he wears a clown mask, his flamboyant attire allows you to instantly recognize him as a bishop wanted by both the Coalition and TSM. Looking around, you decided to listen to what kind of favor he's going to ask.</tsm.a81>
  <tsm.a82>I was heading to the next outpost, but the channel is blocked by T.S.M right now. I have something very important to do there, if... I mean, if you could help deal with them...</tsm.a82>
  <tsm.a83>It would depend on how sincere you'd like to be.</tsm.a83>
  <tsm.a84>Oh! My friend, I can be as sincere as you want me to be.</tsm.a84>
  <tsm.a8a>You recognize him as a wanted man and handcuff him.</tsm.a8a>
  <tsm.a8b>"You asshole, do you know where you are! This is not the territory of your The Seditionists of Mendacity! Somebody, somebody!" The bishop yells over, and everyone around you leans toward you with all kinds of weapons.</tsm.a8b>
  <tsm.a8c>You have a bad feeling and are about to flee when an explosion goes off and the Coalition Riot Suppression Force invades from all over the place.</tsm.a8c>
  <tsm.a8d>While you're still in a daze, you hear from a walkie-talkie, "Empty the room, leave no one alive!"</tsm.a8d>
  <tsm.b8>Ignore him and leave.</tsm.b8>
  <tsm.lq>Getting the job done</tsm.lq>
  <!--黑市商人-->
  <tsm8.s1>I'm the black market merchant at this outpost. Come check out if I have what you're looking for?</tsm8.s1>
  <tsm8.exchange>View Merchandise</tsm8.exchange>
  <tsm8.leave>Not interested, leave.</tsm8.leave>
  <tsm8.welcome>Come back soon!</tsm8.welcome>
  <tsm8.praise1>That's all I have for now.</tsm8.praise1>
  <tsm8.praise2>Fair prices, no tricks for anyone!</tsm8.praise2>
  <tsm8.moneyless>No money? Then get the hell out of here!</tsm8.moneyless>
  <tsm8.exchange.suger.hhq>400MK for Sugar's Transmogrifier</tsm8.exchange.suger.hhq>
  <tsm8.exchange.suger.combatuniform>300MK for Tom Sugar Combat Uniform</tsm8.exchange.suger.combatuniform>
  <tsm8.exchange.suger.colthes>250MK for Tom Sugar Hoodie</tsm8.exchange.suger.colthes>
  <tsm8.exchange.suger.hat>150MK for Naval First Mate's Hat</tsm8.exchange.suger.hat>
  <tsm8.exchange.suger.axe>450MK for Tom Sugar's Battle Axe</tsm8.exchange.suger.axe>
  <tsm8.exchange.suger.handgun>1400MK for Icarus Hand Cannon</tsm8.exchange.suger.handgun>
  <tsm8.exchange.lerentine.hhq>400MK for Lerentine's Transmogrifier</tsm8.exchange.lerentine.hhq>
  <tsm8.exchange.lerentine.handgun>1400MK for Gray-Eyed Hand Cannon</tsm8.exchange.lerentine.handgun>
  <tsm8.exchange.handgunammo>700MK for 6 rounds of Hand Cannon Ammunition</tsm8.exchange.handgunammo>
  <tsm8.exchange.tsm_fkj_g3a4>1750MK for G3A3 Battle Rifle</tsm8.exchange.tsm_fkj_g3a4>
  <tsm8.exchange.tsm_fkj_fal>1750MK for FAL "Pharaoh" Battle Rifle</tsm8.exchange.tsm_fkj_fal>
  <tsm8.exchange.tsm_fkj_ace52>2000MK for Galil ACE52 Battle Rifle</tsm8.exchange.tsm_fkj_ace52>
  <tsm8.exchange.tsm_fkj_sg553>2000MK for SG542 "Raider" Rifle</tsm8.exchange.tsm_fkj_sg553>
  <!--黑船-->
  <tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.c1>While you were strolling leisurely, a person dressed as an alliance soldier called out to you from behind</tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.c1>
  <tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.o1>Are you calling me? What's the matter?</tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.o1>
  <tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.o1.c1>We need to take your ship to the next station. If you can take us, we can pay you 5000 mk</tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.o1.c1>
  <tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.o2>Well... I need to ask my crew. If it's possible, we will call you when we leave the port</tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.o2>
  <tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.o3>No problem, we will wait for your news</tsm_opdeco_hrflyers_1.o3>
  <!--摄魂空间对话-->
  <tsm_space_shehun_q1>Hello there, friend</tsm_space_shehun_q1>
  <tsm_space_shehun_q2>Yes, yes! Have you heard of the Dementonite Space?</tsm_space_shehun_q2>
  <tsm_space_shehun_q3>Whether you know me doesn’t matter, but I know you. How about you chat with me for a bit? An old man like me just craves some company every now and then.</tsm_space_shehun_q3>
  <tsm_space_shehun_q4>You’re partially right. It has no fixed physical coordinates and cannot be reached through conventional means. From a dimensional science perspective, the Dementonite Space is a "Consciousness Dimension" parallel to the material universe, yet it also has a physical aspect. Take the containers we use, for example—many of them are made from Dementonite Wrench. They look small, but can hold far more than their size suggests. That’s because the ore’s unique properties transfer those objects into that very dimension.</tsm_space_shehun_q4>
  <tsm_space_shehun_q5>Do you think we could ever enter the Dementonite Space?</tsm_space_shehun_q5>
  <tsm_space_shehun_q6>Nothing is absolute. It has no fixed coordinates, but we can create anchors. Of course, the most crucial step to get in is to have a "Gate".</tsm_space_shehun_q6>
  <tsm_space_shehun_q7>Exactly. With a Gate, not only can we enter that dimension—we can even drag an entire area into it.</tsm_space_shehun_q7>
  <tsm_space_shehun_q8>There’s so much more to say about all this. Time’s running out, I’m afraid I have to go now. Thank you for chatting with me for so long, friend. I can’t let you waste your time for nothing—here, take this crate as a gift.</tsm_space_shehun_q8>
  <tsm_space_shehun_q9>Names don’t matter, but you can call me Doctors.</tsm_space_shehun_q9>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a1>Did you call me?</tsm_space_shehun_a1>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a2>Wait, hold on—don’t talk about the Dementonite Space yet. Do I even know you?</tsm_space_shehun_a2>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a3>Fine, fine. The Dementonite Space... I’ve only ever heard of it. Isn’t it some kind of place that doesn’t exist in our timeline, or even our dimension?</tsm_space_shehun_a3>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a4>So that’s how it works.</tsm_space_shehun_a4>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a5>That’s impossible, isn’t it? You just said it has no physical coordinates and can’t be reached.</tsm_space_shehun_a5>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a6>A Gate?</tsm_space_shehun_a6>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a7>That sounds terrifying. Like, you could be asleep one second, then wake up in a whole different world.So what is this Gate, anyway? Do we have to find it, or can we build it ourselves?</tsm_space_shehun_a7>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a8>Oh right, I still don’t know your name.</tsm_space_shehun_a8>
  <tsm_space_shehun_a9>What a strange old man.</tsm_space_shehun_a9>
  <!--54区会议-->
  <tsm_eyi_54_jm>A broadcast blares from the communicator. "Calling all crew members of the newly docked vessel. Please proceed to the main office—your attendance is required at a meeting."</tsm_eyi_54_jm>

  <tsm_54_hy_q1>As you step into the conference room, you spot several personnel standing by, reviewing their respective communication panels. Catching sight of you, the controller immediately reports into their panel: "Chairman, all attendees have arrived."</tsm_54_hy_q1>
  <tsm_54_hy_q2>"Very well, noted. Make this quick—first, report on the current situation in Sector 54."</tsm_54_hy_q2>
  <tsm_54_hy_q3>"Greetings, Chairman Zhang and esteemed colleagues. I am the administrator of Sector 54. Recently, abnormal activity has been detected within the Potent Plague Eliminator-infected zones of our sector, and an unknown signal source resembling a 'Beacon' was identified at the epicenter of the infection. Needless to say, the threat posed by such a Beacon speaks for itself."</tsm_54_hy_q3>
  <tsm_54_hy_q4>"A 'Beacon' is the core of a Broodmother, the critical node where Potent Plague Eliminator entities converge and form. It emits a 'broadcast' signal that accelerates the Potent Plague Eliminator's mutation process while enabling control over infected organisms—these are the key details we have ascertained thus far." Pausing briefly, he continues his report: "Currently, the infected area in Sector 54 is expanding relentlessly, posing a direct threat to our sector's pharmaceutical and ammunition production facilities. As a result, worker panic has spread, leading to mass resignations. If this trend persists, it will trigger a crisis of supply disruption for related materials; in the worst-case scenario, the infected zone may expand to cover 50% of the entire sector."</tsm_54_hy_q4>
  <tsm_54_hy_q5>"Can we restart production lines in Sector 33?"</tsm_54_hy_q5>
  <tsm_54_hy_q6>"Greetings, Chairman Zhang. Sector 33 is located adjacent to the war zone between the Alliance and the Rebels, making raw material transportation extremely high-risk. Furthermore, all equipment in the sector is outdated, and its production capacity is completely unable to meet our requirements. Restarting operations is not feasible at this time."</tsm_54_hy_q6>
  <tsm_54_hy_q7>"In that case, it seems we cannot afford to abandon Sector 54. Is Lin Ye present? As the earliest sector to be contained and managed, does Sector 73 have any viable solutions to offer?"</tsm_54_hy_q7>
  <tsm_54_hy_q8>"Greetings, Chairman Zhang. The situation in Sector 73 is fundamentally different from that of Sector 54—we completed the construction of our 'Isolation Gate' defense system years ago, and our Potent Plague Eliminator-infected zones have been in a frozen state long-term. Regular clearance of peripheral nests is sufficient to effectively contain Potent Plague Eliminator expansion and ensure the operation of frontline bases." He then shifts his tone: "That said, I have a proposal—would it be possible to deploy Gravity Throwers to carry out long-range strikes?"</tsm_54_hy_q8>
  <tsm_54_hy_q9>"That plan is not viable. We cannot safely deploy a Gravity Thrower strike team to an effective combat position. Additionally, Team Two 'White Hoof Crow' is on standby at headquarters, while Teams One and Three are both on active missions—no support can be redeployed in the short term."</tsm_54_hy_q9>
  <tsm_54_hy_q10>Everyone turns toward the sound of the voice as a man pushes open the door and enters.
    "Lei Sefen, you're late."</tsm_54_hy_q10>
  <tsm_54_hy_q11>"I wasn't exactly invited to this meeting, was I? Setting that aside—I'm here to present a plan. The follow-up experiments at San ShenQiu have been a resounding success; we now have seven qualified operators. As for 'Sea Conqueror', we currently have five units in our possession. If the board approves, I can immediately begin deployment preparations."</tsm_54_hy_q11>
  <tsm_54_hy_q12>"So this experiment has finally borne fruit after all. How controllable are the personnel? What degree of certainty do you have in resolving the crisis in Sector 54?"</tsm_54_hy_q12>
  <tsm_54_hy_q13>"Chairman Zhang, the controllability rate is approximately 70%. If executed according to plan, I have 100% confidence in resolving the issue."</tsm_54_hy_q13>
  <tsm_54_hy_q14>His gaze lands on you as he steps forward slowly, offering a hand: "Greetings. I am Lei Sefen from headquarters. I don't believe we've met before. Still, the fact that a non-staff personnel is allowed to attend this core meeting speaks volumes about your capabilities."</tsm_54_hy_q14>
  <tsm_54_hy_q15>Lei Sefen lets out a faint chuckle: "In the current climate, 'luck' alone hardly cuts it. Since you're willing to contribute to TSM, you're one of us. If you ever need assistance in the future, don't hesitate to contact me." With that, he turns and exits the room.</tsm_54_hy_q15>

  <tsm_jx>Continue</tsm_jx>
  <tsm_54_hy_a1>You cut in abruptly: "Excuse me, but could someone please explain exactly what a 'Beacon' is?"</tsm_54_hy_a1>
  <tsm_54_hy_a2>You open your mouth to add further clarification, but a voice suddenly interrupts the proceedings: "I have a suggestion."</tsm_54_hy_a2>
  <tsm_54_hy_a3>Just got lucky with handling a few tricky situations—that's all. Nothing worth mentioning.</tsm_54_hy_a3>
  <!--军需官对话-->
  <tsm.wait>Come back later.</tsm.wait>
  <tsm.wait1></tsm.wait1>
  <tsm.no.id>You don't have T.S.M Allied Identification Code on you. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.no.id>
  <tsm.no.faction>You don't have enough reputation. Please don't waste my time.</tsm.no.faction>
  <tsm.no.faction50>Sorry, to redeem the Tritium Core Sealer, your TSM reputation must be greater than 50.</tsm.no.faction50>
  <tsm.dh.faction.25>You have to have at least 25 reputation to be able to exchange supplies.</tsm.dh.faction.25>
  <tsm.jxg.help>Hello, I'm the Quartermaster of T.SM. How can I help you?</tsm.jxg.help>
  <tsm.dh.yjsbm>Redeeming items with T.S.M Allied Identification Code</tsm.dh.yjsbm>
  <tsm.dh.faction>Redeem items with T.S.M reputation</tsm.dh.faction>
  <tsm.dh.vip>VIP service</tsm.dh.vip>
  <tsm.dh.vip.js>When your reputation reaches a certain level, we will assign professional bodyguards to provide you with a full range of personal security protection services.</tsm.dh.vip.js>
  <tsm.dh.vip.60.success>Greetings to our valued customers! You have become our valued VIP customer, we will provide special security protection for you, PiFu will follow you, for your safety and rights and interests.</tsm.dh.vip.60.success>
  <tsm.dh.vip.60.failure> channel has been blocked by T.S.M. Please return immediately or we will expel you by force!m.dh.vip.60.failure&gt;Dear Customer, Hello! After checking your reputation value, it has not yet reached 60, failing to meet the standard of VIP service. We deeply regret this and thank you for your understanding and support!</tsm.dh.vip.60.failure>
  <tsm.dh.vip.success>Respectfully, PiFu are already on your crew list</tsm.dh.vip.success>
  <tsm.dh.vip.rd.success>PiFu:Hello, sir. It's an honor to serve you!</tsm.dh.vip.rd.success>
  <tsm.over>Please put your belongings away.</tsm.over>
  <tsm.dh.xh1>Because of the current chaos of war between various forces, the situation is very unpromising, so for the time being, we can only exchange these</tsm.dh.xh1>
  <tsm.dh.xh2>Fair price, fair and square</tsm.dh.xh2>
  <tsm.dh.xbz>Welcome to T.S.M Supply Beacon Station. How may I help you?</tsm.dh.xbz>
  <tsm.dh.kw>Redemption of mineral supplies</tsm.dh.kw>
  <tsm.dh.yl>Redemption of medical supplies</tsm.dh.yl>
  <tsm.dh.dy>Redemption of ammunition supplies</tsm.dh.dy>
  <tsm.dh.hw>Redemption of escort services</tsm.dh.hw>
  <tsm.dh.bg>Redemption of Tritium Core Packs</tsm.dh.bg>
  <tsm.dh.jiuzhou>edemption of Jiuzhou Set</tsm.dh.jiuzhou>
  <tsm.dh.nujiang>edemption of Nujiang Set</tsm.dh.nujiang>
  <tsm.dh.mingfu>edemption of Mingfu Set</tsm.dh.mingfu>
  <tsm.dh.niaochao>edemption of Brid Nest SET</tsm.dh.niaochao>
  <tsm.d1>The current number of licenses issued by our department is several times that of the past. But there is no other way. The war has begun, and the situation is critical everywhere. We hope the war will end soon.</tsm.d1>
  <tsm.d2>Sorry, you do not have an official license. If you make such a joke again, you will be arrested.</tsm.d2>
  <!--test:航道封锁-->
  <tsm.warming1.1>This channel has been blocked by T.S.M. Please return immediately or we will expel you by force!</tsm.warming1.1>
  <tsm.warming1.2>Last warning! Please return to your flight immediately!</tsm.warming1.2>
  <!--test:站点入侵-->
  <tsm.outpost_invasions.1>You see a man sneaking around, so you go up to see what he's up to.</tsm.outpost_invasions.1>
  <tsm.outpost_invasions.cancel>Ignore him and walk away.</tsm.outpost_invasions.cancel>
  <tsm.outpost_invasions.1.1>What are you doing?” You're putting your hand on his shoulder as you talk.</tsm.outpost_invasions.1.1>
  <tsm.outpost_invasions.1.2>“Don't run!” You hadn't taken two steps in pursuit when the station began to sound an alarm</tsm.outpost_invasions.1.2>
  <tsm.outpost_invasions.1.3>T.S.M:\n has detected an invasion by unknown forces and has now activated the T-71 defense protocols, with the entire site in lockdown. All citizens are requested to remain calm and proceed immediately to the nearest safe haven. The Sunset Combat Department will be launching a full-scale cleanup operation against the invaders, so please refrain from acting without authorization and wait patiently for the situation to recover.</tsm.outpost_invasions.1.3>
  <!--test:任务事件-->
  <tsm_fire_water_1>You feel extraordinarily hot outside the submarine, and before long you're sweating profusely, reaching out to touch the outer shell only to be scalded and retract your hand...looks like there's something out there that's making the water boil? \n I guess I'll have to put on my wetsuit soon</tsm_fire_water_1>
  <!--test:角色-->
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_1>Captain of Wolf Falcon Squad</npctitle.TSMnpc_1>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_1>Lang</charactername.TSMnpc_1>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_2>Captain of Shadow-Stained Squad</npctitle.TSMnpc_2>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_2>Youmu</charactername.TSMnpc_2>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_3>EMBI Liaison Officer</charactername.TSMnpc_3>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_4>Chief Instructor of TSM</npctitle.TSMnpc_4>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_4>Tom Suger</charactername.TSMnpc_4>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_5>Jiuzhou Operations Department</npctitle.TSMnpc_5>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_5>Lerentine</charactername.TSMnpc_5>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_6></charactername.TSMnpc_6>
  <npctitle.TSMnpc_7>Advent Faction</npctitle.TSMnpc_7>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_7>Pelavin</charactername.TSMnpc_7>
  <charactername.TSMnpc_8>Black Market Merchant</charactername.TSMnpc_8>
  <npctitle.tsm_vip_bodyguard_1>TSM VIP Bodyguard</npctitle.tsm_vip_bodyguard_1>
  <charactername.tsm_vip_bodyguard_1>PiFu</charactername.tsm_vip_bodyguard_1>
  <npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_police>Outpost Police</npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_police>
  <npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_sunset>Sunset Operations Department</npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_sunset>
  <npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_advanced>Advanced Operations Department</npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_advanced>
  <npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_nujiang>Outpost Assault Squadron</npctitle.tsm_outpost_combat_nujiang>
  <npctitle.tsm_outpostmanager>Controller</npctitle.tsm_outpostmanager>
  <npctitle.tsm_wz_ff>Quartermaster</npctitle.tsm_wz_ff>
  <npctitle.tsm_caretakers>Route Manager</npctitle.tsm_caretakers>
  <npctitle.tsm_wz_ff_xbz>Beacon Station Manager</npctitle.tsm_wz_ff_xbz>
  <npctitle.tsm_bountyhunter>TSM Bounty Task Distributor</npctitle.tsm_bountyhunter>
  <npctitle.tsm_gendarmerie>TSM Military Police</npctitle.tsm_gendarmerie>
  <npctitle.tsmnpc_lin>Electrical Engineer</npctitle.tsmnpc_lin>
  <charactername.tsmnpc_lin>Lin He Yin</charactername.tsmnpc_lin>
  <charactername.tsm_yan>Yan</charactername.tsm_yan>
  <charactername.tsm_chris>Chris Evans</charactername.tsm_chris>
  <npctitle.tsm_54>Head of the TSM Region</npctitle.tsm_54>
  <charactername.tsm_lsf>Leseffen</charactername.tsm_lsf>
  <!--插板-->
  <entityname.tsm_armor_allbuff>TSM Tech - All-Purpose Armor Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_allbuff>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_allbuff>An all-purpose armor plate developed by Moer Yous, integrating various types of armor protection to achieve more comprehensive defensive effects. However, compared to single-type protection, it is more prone to damage and does not reach the highest level of protection.</entitydescription.tsm_armor_allbuff>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_bleeding>TSM Tech - Bleeding Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_bleeding>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_bleeding>Bleeding Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Bleeding\n\nProtection Level: 60%-80%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_bleeding>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_lacerations>TSM Tech - Laceration Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_lacerations>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_lacerations>Laceration Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Lacerations\n\nProtection Level: 55%-75%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_lacerations>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_stun>TSM Tech - Stun Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_stun>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_stun>Stun Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Stun\n\nProtection Level: 30%-50%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_stun>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_blunttrauma>TSM Tech - Blunt Trauma Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_blunttrauma>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_blunttrauma>Blunt Trauma Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Blunt Trauma\n\nProtection Level: 50%-70%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_blunttrauma>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_huskinfection>TSM Tech - Husk Infection Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_huskinfection>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_huskinfection>Husk Virus Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Husk Virus\n\nProtection Level: 100%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_huskinfection>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_paralysis>TSM Tech - Paralysis Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_paralysis>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_paralysis>Paralysis Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Paralysis\n\nProtection Level: 70%-90%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_paralysis>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_triton>TSM Tech - Triton Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_triton>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_triton>Special Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Triton/Burst\n\nProtection Level: 55%-70%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_triton>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_bitewounds>TSM Tech - Bite Wound Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_bitewounds>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_bitewounds>Bite Wound Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Bite Wounds\n\nProtection Level: 55%-75%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_bitewounds>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_explosiondamage>TSM Tech - Explosion Damage Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_explosiondamage>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_explosiondamage>Deep Tissue Damage Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Deep Tissue Damage\n\nProtection Level: 50%-70%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_explosiondamage>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_gunshotwound>TSM Tech - Gunshot Wound Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_gunshotwound>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_gunshotwound>Gunshot Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Gunshot Wounds\n\nProtection Level: 50%-70%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_gunshotwound>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_poisons>TSM Tech - Poison Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_poisons>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_poisons>Poison Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Gunshot Wounds\n\nProtection Level: 80%-100%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_poisons>
  <entityname.tsm_armor_burn>TSM Tech - Burn Protection Plate</entityname.tsm_armor_burn>
  <entitydescription.tsm_armor_burn>Burn Protection Armor Plate\n\nDevelopment Location: Jiuzhou Arsenal\n\nProtection Type: Gunshot Wounds\n\nProtection Level: 50%-60%</entitydescription.tsm_armor_burn>
  <!--背包/容器-->
  <entityname.tsm_metalcrate>TSM Freight Crate</entityname.tsm_metalcrate>
  <entitydescription.tsm_metalcrate>Large capacity, multi-purpose, fireproof and waterproof, reliable quality.</entitydescription.tsm_metalcrate>
  <entityname.tsm_toolbox>TSM Toolbox</entityname.tsm_toolbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_toolbox>Large capacity briefcase, made from exotic materials, with free after-sales service available.</entitydescription.tsm_toolbox>
  <entityname.tsm_weaponbackpack>Weapon Case</entityname.tsm_weaponbackpack>
  <entitydescription.tsm_weaponbackpack>Features 9 slots, which can be used to store weapons, ammunition, or diving suits, and can also be worn on the back.</entitydescription.tsm_weaponbackpack>
  <entityname.tsm_bag_medium>Concert Tactical Backpack</entityname.tsm_bag_medium>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bag_medium>A tactical backpack with moderate capacity.</entitydescription.tsm_bag_medium>
  <entityname.tsm_bag_small>Backpack</entityname.tsm_bag_small>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bag_small>A multi-purpose small-capacity backpack, easy to make but with limited space.</entitydescription.tsm_bag_small>
  <entityname.tsm_bag_big>Tactical Backpack</entityname.tsm_bag_big>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bag_big>Can hold a large amount of ammunition and a heavy weapon, effectively enhancing a soldier's sustained combat capability.</entitydescription.tsm_bag_big>
  <entityname.tsm_bag_heavy>Heavy Load Backpack</entityname.tsm_bag_heavy>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bag_heavy>A large bag that can hold many items and attach a toolbox and a heavy gun. It will slightly affect the use of weapons and submarine driving.</entitydescription.tsm_bag_heavy>
  <entityname.tsm_bag_heavy_big>Large Transport Backpack</entityname.tsm_bag_heavy_big>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bag_heavy_big>An even larger backpack that can hold two toolboxes and two heavy guns. However, its large size makes it inconvenient to use weapons and drive submarines when worn.</entitydescription.tsm_bag_heavy_big>
  <entityname.tsm_bag_diving_special>Coalition Special Operations Backpack</entityname.tsm_bag_diving_special>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bag_diving_special>A type of backpack issued only to elite members of some special forces within the Coalition. It has moderate capacity but features two dedicated slots for diving suits and a specific attachment point for heavy weapons. However, its large size will affect weapon use.</entitydescription.tsm_bag_diving_special>
  <entityname.tsm_bag_diving>Special Operations Backpack</entityname.tsm_bag_diving>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bag_diving>Has moderate capacity with a dedicated space for diving suits. Its large size will affect weapon use.</entitydescription.tsm_bag_diving>
  <entityname.tsm_bag_diving_big>Large Special Operations Backpack</entityname.tsm_bag_diving_big>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bag_diving_big>A larger-capacity backpack with a dedicated space for diving suits. However, it is inconvenient to use tools for submarine maintenance when worn.</entitydescription.tsm_bag_diving_big>
  <entityname.tsm_danger_box>TSM Anomaly Containment Box</entityname.tsm_danger_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_danger_box>Container specialized for anomalous objects.</entitydescription.tsm_danger_box>
  <entityname.tsm_trolley>All-Purpose Cart</entityname.tsm_trolley>
  <entitydescription.tsm_trolley>Made of tough plastic, it can carry a lot and won’t rust in seawater. When not in use, just stick it to the wall so it won’t slide around. Pop in a battery and it turns into a little lamp. The sub’s supply crew loves it. Don’t sit on it—if you do and get hurt, that’s on you.</entitydescription.tsm_trolley>
  <entityname.tsm_trashcan>Trash Can</entityname.tsm_trashcan>
  <entitydescription.tsm_trashcan>Drop the junk you hate—like that stupid clown horn—inside, slam the lid, and forget it. Letting go is the only way to move on.</entitydescription.tsm_trashcan>
  <!--物品-->
  <entityname.tsm_lighter>Old Lighter</entityname.tsm_lighter>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lighter>Want to smoke a cigarette?</entitydescription.tsm_lighter>
  <entityname.tsm_marlboro_cigar>Marlboro Cigarette</entityname.tsm_marlboro_cigar>
  <entitydescription.tsm_marlboro_cigar>Man always remember love because of romantic only\nSlowly reduces mental stress, psychosis, and delirium poisoning</entitydescription.tsm_marlboro_cigar>
  <entityname.tsm_marlboro_box>Pack of Marlboro</entityname.tsm_marlboro_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_marlboro_box>Smoking Marlboro gives you more masculinity\nContains 8 Marlboro cigarettes</entitydescription.tsm_marlboro_box>
  <entityname.tsm_Chinese_cigar>Huazi Cigarette</entityname.tsm_Chinese_cigar>
  <entitydescription.tsm_Chinese_cigar>Every puff of Huazi shows noble quality\nQuickly relieves mental stress and psychosis, and provides resistance to mental stress</entitydescription.tsm_Chinese_cigar>
  <entityname.tsm_Chinesecigar_box>Pack of Huazi</entityname.tsm_Chinesecigar_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_Chinesecigar_box>Distinct character, elegant style, beauty of Huazi\nContains 6 Huazi cigarettes</entitydescription.tsm_Chinesecigar_box>
  <entityname.tsm_universe_cigar>Cosmos Cigarette</entityname.tsm_universe_cigar>
  <entitydescription.tsm_universe_cigar>The top choice for superhumans on Europa\nQuickly relieves mental stress and delirium poisoning</entitydescription.tsm_universe_cigar>
  <entityname.tsm_universe_box>Pack of Cosmos</entityname.tsm_universe_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_universe_box>Smoke Cosmos, become a Europa person\nContains 6 Cosmos cigarettes</entitydescription.tsm_universe_box>
  <entityname.tsm_identifier>T.S.M Allied Identification Code</entityname.tsm_identifier>
  <entitydescription.tsm_identifier>A common identification code within T.S.M, which you can request various services from T.S.M logistics department</entitydescription.tsm_identifier>
  <!--恶疫相关-->
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_relics>Plague Organism</entityname.tsm_eyi_relics>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_relics>A product not belonging to this world, might need an abnormal affairs containment box</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_relics>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_glandular>Skeletal Remains</entityname.tsm_eyi_glandular>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_glandular>Used for crafting stimulants related to the Plague.</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_glandular>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_embryo>Flesh Embryo</entityname.tsm_eyi_embryo>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_embryo></entitydescription.tsm_eyi_embryo>
  <entityname.tsm_needletube_empty>Empty Syringe</entityname.tsm_needletube_empty>
  <entitydescription.tsm_needletube_empty></entitydescription.tsm_needletube_empty>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_helmet>Plague Protection Helmet</entityname.tsm_eyi_helmet>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_helmet>Protective helmet for Plague researchers. Reduces the risk of infection significantly while providing decent protection against hostile creatures.</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_helmet>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_suit>Plague Protection Suit</entityname.tsm_eyi_suit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_suit>Protective suit for Plague researchers. Provides protection against Plague infection and water pressure.</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_suit>
  <entityname.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>Plague Type III Suppressant</entityname.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>
  <entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>Used to suppress the growth of flesh embryos and prevent them from entering the next stage, but it cannot fully cure</entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>
  <entityname.tsm_virusstage_clear>Plague Potent Eliminator</entityname.tsm_virusstage_clear>
  <entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_clear>Directly removes flesh embryos from the body, but causes physical harm.</entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_clear>
  <entityname.tsm_virusstage_deep_inhibitory>Potent Plague Eliminator</entityname.tsm_virusstage_deep_inhibitory>
  <entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_deep_inhibitory>Used for potent elimination of the plague (Flesh Embryo Stage 2), at the cost of significant bodily harm.</entitydescription.tsm_virusstage_deep_inhibitory>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent>Plague Norm</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent>Stable state: Dormant inside your body, will accelerate transformation if injected with living plague\nA norm developed by TSM to enhance the human body, with different effects at various stages</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_1>Plague Stability Enhancer</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_1>An enhancer from an unknown origin, its purpose to increase or decrease plague norm stability is unclear</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_1>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_2>Plague Stability Enhancer</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_2>An enhancer from an unknown origin, its purpose to increase or decrease plague norm stability is unclear</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_reagent_2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_1>Plague Reinforcement Enhancer I</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_1>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:255,110,0,255‖increase stability by 1‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_1>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_2>Plague Reinforcement Enhancer II</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_2>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:255,110,0,255‖increase stability by 2‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_3>Plague Reinforcement Enhancer III</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_3>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_3>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:255,110,0,255‖increase stability by 3‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_3>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_4>Plague Reinforcement Enhancer IV</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_4>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_4>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:255,110,0,255‖increase stability by 4‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_add_4>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_1>Plague Weakening Enhancer I</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_1>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:0,255,110,255‖decrease stability by 1‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_1>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_2>Plague Weakening Enhancer II</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_2>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:0,255,110,255‖decrease stability by 2‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_2>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_3>Plague Weakening Enhancer III</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_3>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_3>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:0,255,110,255‖decrease stability by 3‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_3>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_4>Plague Weakening Enhancer IV</entityname.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_4>
  <entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_4>Stability enhancer, each use will‖color:0,255,110,255‖decrease stability by 4‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_eyi_stabilise_diminish_4>
  <!--矿物/金属-->
  <entityname.tsm_tungstenore>Tungsten Ore</entityname.tsm_tungstenore>
  <entitydescription.tsm_tungstenore></entitydescription.tsm_tungstenore>
  <entityname.tsm_tungsten>Tungsten</entityname.tsm_tungsten>
  <entitydescription.tsm_tungsten></entitydescription.tsm_tungsten>
  <entityname.tsm_sulphurore>Sulphur Ore</entityname.tsm_sulphurore>
  <entitydescription.tsm_sulphurore></entitydescription.tsm_sulphurore>
  <entityname.tsm_sulphur>Sulphur</entityname.tsm_sulphur>
  <entitydescription.tsm_sulphur></entitydescription.tsm_sulphur>
  <entityname.tsm_kore>Alien Ore</entityname.tsm_kore>
  <entitydescription.tsm_kore>Uncommon and strange mineral clusters, which can be broken down into different materials.</entitydescription.tsm_kore>
  <entityname.tsm_oilshaleore>Oilshale Ore</entityname.tsm_oilshaleore>
  <entitydescription.tsm_oilshaleore></entitydescription.tsm_oilshaleore>
  <entityname.tsm_oilshale>Oilshale</entityname.tsm_oilshale>
  <entitydescription.tsm_oilshale></entitydescription.tsm_oilshale>
  <entityname.tsm_yx_crystallography>Crystallography</entityname.tsm_yx_crystallography>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yx_crystallography>Tempered from the streaming light of the deep sea into sharp crystal edges; cyan mist and abyssal blue twist into its grain, while starlit iridescence wraps the faint light of dawn and dusk. To touch it is like holding the sea within mist—hidden in its icy texture is the heartbeat of the tides.</entitydescription.tsm_yx_crystallography>
  <entityname.tsm_hengberley_star>Hengberley Star</entityname.tsm_hengberley_star>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hengberley_star>Indigo overlaps with dark emerald veins; the crystal surface ripples with the cold rainbow unique to the abyss. The algal traces tangled at its base are the silent palm lines of the deep sea. A brush of the fingertip feels like touching the tide floor unthawed for millennia—trapped in its frigid crystal core is the lingering echo of slumbering ocean currents.</entitydescription.tsm_hengberley_star>
  <!--杂物-->
  <entityname.tsm_pq>Paint</entityname.tsm_pq>
  <entitydescription.tsm_pq>The large industrial equipment at the site is capable of manufacturing it, and you can use it to apply your favorite paint job to firearms.</entitydescription.tsm_pq>
  <entityname.tsm_lm_weaponbox>Coalition Weaponbox</entityname.tsm_lm_weaponbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lm_weaponbox>It contains some general-purpose parts and disposable tools, which can be used to manufacture and modify the standard weapons of the coalition.</entitydescription.tsm_lm_weaponbox>
  <entityname.tsm_yh_weaponbox>Separatists Weaponbox</entityname.tsm_yh_weaponbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yh_weaponbox>It contains some general-purpose parts and disposable tools, which can be used to manufacture and modify the standard weapons of the separatists.</entitydescription.tsm_yh_weaponbox>
  <entityname.tsm_handgun_box>Pistol Kit</entityname.tsm_handgun_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_handgun_box>A set of generic pistol rough models that can be customized into the desired pistol according to your needs.</entitydescription.tsm_handgun_box>
  <entityname.tsm_plastic>Engineering Plastic</entityname.tsm_plastic>
  <entitydescription.tsm_plastic>Engineering plastics possess excellent comprehensive properties, with high rigidity, low creep, high mechanical strength, good heat resistance, and good electrical insulation. They can be used as engineering structural materials in harsh chemical and physical environments for extended periods, and can even replace metals in certain applications.</entitydescription.tsm_plastic>
  <entityname.tsm_pyrotechnic>Pyrotechnic</entityname.tsm_pyrotechnic>
  <entitydescription.tsm_pyrotechnic>Refine from normal typr of it,provide stronger effect.</entitydescription.tsm_pyrotechnic>
  <entityname.tsm_item_box>Parts Box</entityname.tsm_item_box>
  <entitydescription.tsm_item_box>A small box containing a variety of parts.</entitydescription.tsm_item_box>
  <entityname.tsm_hpc>High-precision components</entityname.tsm_hpc>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hpc></entitydescription.tsm_hpc>
  <entityname.tsm_ic>Integrated Circuit</entityname.tsm_ic>
  <entitydescription.tsm_ic>High-precision circuit boards, mostly in stock, are used for manufacturing various instruments.</entitydescription.tsm_ic>
  <entityname.tsm_hydrocarbons>Barreled fuel and gas.</entityname.tsm_hydrocarbons>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hydrocarbons></entitydescription.tsm_hydrocarbons>
  <entityname.tsm_radiojammer>Radiojammer</entityname.tsm_radiojammer>
  <entitydescription.tsm_radiojammer>Stop jamming by throwing it out of the container</entitydescription.tsm_radiojammer>
  <entityname.tsm_blueprint>Coalition Weapon Blueprint</entityname.tsm_blueprint>
  <entitydescription.tsm_blueprint>It contains the blueprints for the standard weapons of the coalition, which can be used as a reference for manufacturing the standard weapons of the coalition.</entitydescription.tsm_blueprint>
  <entityname.tsm_blueprint1>TSM Weapon Blueprint</entityname.tsm_blueprint1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_blueprint1>It contains the blueprints for the standard weapons of the TSM, which can be used as a reference for manufacturing the standard weapons of the TSM.</entitydescription.tsm_blueprint1>
  <entityname.tsm_zc_1>Part of The Battle Wagon</entityname.tsm_zc_1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_zc_1></entitydescription.tsm_zc_1>
  <entityname.tsm_zc_2>Part of The Battle Wagon</entityname.tsm_zc_2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_zc_2></entitydescription.tsm_zc_2>
  <entityname.tsm_zc_3>Part of The Battle Wagon</entityname.tsm_zc_3>
  <entitydescription.tsm_zc_3></entitydescription.tsm_zc_3>
  <entityname.tsm_zc_4>Part of The Battle Wagon</entityname.tsm_zc_4>
  <entitydescription.tsm_zc_4></entitydescription.tsm_zc_4>
  <entityname.tsm_triton_bag>TSM tritium core sealer</entityname.tsm_triton_bag>
  <entitydescription.tsm_triton_bag>Seal the tritium core for use in crafting items related to the Tritium Bullet at the workbench. This packaging cannot completely prevent the leakage of the tritium core inside. It needs to be placed inside the TeraSynergy Matrix Anomalous Object Containment Box to avoid being burned.</entitydescription.tsm_triton_bag>
  <!--制作台-->
  <entityname.tsm_fabricator>Ammunition and Weapon Fabricator</entityname.tsm_fabricator>
  <entitydescription.tsm_fabricator>Can be used to craft TSM weapons and ammunitions\nInstallation method: Hold it in your hand, right-click on the target, and then press the use key (default E key) to install. Remember to connect the power.</entitydescription.tsm_fabricator>
  <entityname.tsm_fabricator_ammo>Ammo Fabricator</entityname.tsm_fabricator_ammo>
  <entitydescription.tsm_fabricator_ammo>A Fabricator specially used to craft Ammos\nInstallation method: Hold it in your hand, right-click on the target, and then press the use key (default E key) to install. Remember to connect the power.</entitydescription.tsm_fabricator_ammo>
  <entityname.tsm_fabricator_quality>Weapon Upgrade Station</entityname.tsm_fabricator_quality>
  <entitydescription.tsm_fabricator_quality>A workstation specifically designed for upgrading firearm quality or modifying firearms.\nInstallation method: Hold it in your hand, right-click on the target, and then press the use key (default E key) to install. Remember to connect the power.</entitydescription.tsm_fabricator_quality>
  <entityname.tsm_fabricator_skin>Skin Fabricator</entityname.tsm_fabricator_skin>
  <entitydescription.tsm_fabricator_skin>A workstation specifically designed for applying paint schemes to firearms, no power required.\nInstallation method: Hold it in your hand, right-click on the target, and then press the use key (default E key) to install.</entitydescription.tsm_fabricator_skin>
  <!--头盔用配件-->
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_thermalgoggles>Thermal goggles for helmets</entityname.tsm_helmet_thermalgoggles>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_thermalgoggles>Unlock Thermal Camera Vision by putting it into your helmet, has a battery inside， charge it when the battery is dead,Normal function can't be enabled if durability below 5%.</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_thermalgoggles>
  <entityname.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_big>Ballistic visor for helmet(large)</entityname.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_big>
  <entitydescription.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_big>Provide better protection to your face when put it into your helmet
    +10% - 35% resistance to gunshot/explosion damage
    +10% weapon spread</entitydescription.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_big>
  <entityname.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_small>Ballistic visor for helmet(small)</entityname.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_small>
  <entitydescription.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_small>Provide better protection to your face when put it into your helmet
    +10% - 35% resistance to gunshot/explosion damage
    +10% weapon spread</entitydescription.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_small>
  <entityname.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_aerjin>Ballistic visor for helmet（Heavy）</entityname.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_aerjin>
  <entitydescription.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_aerjin>Heavy visor: provides substantial head protection, but significantly impairs shooting accuracy.
    +15% - 75% resistance to gunshot/explosion damage
    +25% weapon spread</entitydescription.tsm_ballistic_faceshield_aerjin>
  <entityname.tsm_collider_head>Unpenetrated</entityname.tsm_collider_head>
  <entitydescription.tsm_collider_head></entitydescription.tsm_collider_head>
  <entityname.tsm_protective_jaw>Jaw protetor for helmets</entityname.tsm_protective_jaw>
  <entitydescription.tsm_protective_jaw>Provide protection to your head when put it into your helmet
    +20% resistance to damage/bleeding/stun
    +5% weapon spread</entitydescription.tsm_protective_jaw>
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_diving>Helmet Diving Mask</entityname.tsm_helmet_diving>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_diving>A diving mask for a communication helmet, which can provide oxygen and can also be worn directly on the head.</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_diving>
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_diving1>TSM Helmet Diving Mask</entityname.tsm_helmet_diving1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_diving1>A TSM communication helmet-specific diving mask. It provides oxygen when placed on the communication helmet and cannot be worn directly on the head.</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_diving1>
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_flashlight>Identification device for helmet</entityname.tsm_helmet_flashlight>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_flashlight>Can be put into your helmet to reduce part of your friendly fire damage,Normal function can't be enabled if durability below 5%.\nGive a 10% damage reduce on land to your crew\nGive a 20% reduce in water</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_flashlight>
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_nvd>Night vision device for helmets</entityname.tsm_helmet_nvd>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_nvd>Unlock Night Vision Camera by putting it into your helmet,has a battery inside,charge it if it's dead,Normal function can't be enabled if durability below 5%.</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_nvd>
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_screen>Helmet medical display screen</entityname.tsm_helmet_screen>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_screen>A display that can be putted into a helmet to allow you to monitor the injury status of your crew in real-time.charge it when the battery is dead,Normal function can't be enabled if durability below 5%.</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_screen>
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_diving>Helmet Diving Mask</entityname.tsm_helmet_diving>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_diving>A diving mask for a communication helmet, which can provide oxygen and can also be worn directly on the head.</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_diving>
  <!--药品-->
  <entityname.triton_9C_antidote>Specialized Wound Decontaminant</entityname.triton_9C_antidote>
  <entitydescription.triton_9C_antidote>A special med used to treat Tritium Poisoning,Triton wounds and Burst.</entitydescription.triton_9C_antidote>
  <entityname.tsm_medicalkits>Medical Kit</entityname.tsm_medicalkits>
  <entitydescription.tsm_medicalkits>The standard medical kit produced by TeraSynergy Matrix contains enough medical instruments to handle most common situations on the battlefield, used for treating physical injuries, burns, and bleeding. This kind of medical kit is not expensive, and it is non-refundable and non-exchangeable once sold.</entitydescription.tsm_medicalkits>
  <entityname.tsm_medicalkits_s>Enhanced Medical Kit</entityname.tsm_medicalkits_s>
  <entitydescription.tsm_medicalkits_s>The enhanced medical kit produced by TeraSynergy Matrix contains sufficient medical supplies to perform a battlefield surgery, used for treating physical injuries, burns, and bleeding. This kind of medical kit is expensive, but it is worth the price.</entitydescription.tsm_medicalkits_s>
  <entityname.tsm_anger>Enhanced injection</entityname.tsm_anger>
  <entitydescription.tsm_anger>When used in conjunction with the Operator Assistance System, it can enhance a person's combat capabilities.</entitydescription.tsm_anger>
  <!--补给-->
  <entityname.tsm_pgcflare>Guardian Landing Pod Indicator</entityname.tsm_pgcflare>
  <entitydescription.tsm_pgcflare>'Remember the feeling of distress, call T.S.M'\n\nUsage: Throw it out and wait patiently. (Exists only in one round)</entitydescription.tsm_pgcflare>
  <entityname.tsm_wz_cl_flare>Mineral Supply Drop Indicator</entityname.tsm_wz_cl_flare>
  <entitydescription.tsm_wz_cl_flare>After being thrown, T.S.M will receive a signal and drop a supply pod based on the coordinates</entitydescription.tsm_wz_cl_flare>
  <entityname.tsm_wz_yl_flare>Medical Supply Drop Indicator</entityname.tsm_wz_yl_flare>
  <entitydescription.tsm_wz_yl_flare>After being thrown, T.S.M will receive a signal and drop a medical supply pod based on the coordinates</entitydescription.tsm_wz_yl_flare>
  <entityname.tsm_land_wz_dy>Ammunition drop pod</entityname.tsm_land_wz_dy>
  <entityname.tsm_ammunition_resupply>Ammunition Resupply Indicator</entityname.tsm_ammunition_resupply>
  <entitydescription.tsm_ammunition_resupply>Can spawn a landing pod after using it.</entitydescription.tsm_ammunition_resupply>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment1>T.S.M Mineral Supply Box</entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment1>A common supply box in T.S.M, which randomly yields various common minerals when dismantled\nThese have just been packed and sent from the mines; if you think it's little, I think it's little too</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment1>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment2>T.S.M Mineral Supply Box</entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment2>A common supply box in T.S.M, which randomly yields various common minerals when dismantled\nThese have just been packed and sent from the mines; if you think it's little, I think it's little too</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment2>
  <entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment_med>T.S.M Medical Supply Box</entityname.tsm_mcrate_replenishment_med>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment_med>A common medical supply box in T.S.M, which randomly yields various medical supplies when dismantled\nUrgent! Urgent! The brothers on the front line are still waiting for rescue!</entitydescription.tsm_mcrate_replenishment_med>
  <!--装备：其他-->
  <entityname.tsm_suecide_vest>Suecide Vest</entityname.tsm_suecide_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_suecide_vest>Spreading fear to the world, a 10-second countdown begins once you put it on and activate it.</entitydescription.tsm_suecide_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_bulletproof>Chest rig</entityname.tsm_bulletproof>
  <entitydescription.tsm_bulletproof>Perhaps it was those soldiers who loved to carry a lot of ammunition that couldn't take it anymore. This chest rig appeared on Europa. In exchange for reduced protection, it offers more carrying pouches to hold more items.</entitydescription.tsm_bulletproof>
  <entityname.tsm_medical_vest>Frontline Medic's Bulletproof Vest</entityname.tsm_medical_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_medical_vest>The white bulletproof vest is equipped with numerous carrying pouches for storing medical supplies. These details clearly signal to everyone around that the wearer is a skilled medic. If someone gets injured, they know exactly who to turn to.</entitydescription.tsm_medical_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_general_vest>General bulletproof vest</entityname.tsm_general_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_general_vest>An ordinary bulletproof vest with basic ballistic protection and two carrying pouches.</entitydescription.tsm_general_vest>
  <entityname.pmc_uniform>PMC Combat Uniform</entityname.pmc_uniform>
  <entitydescription.pmc_uniform>As quasi-military personnel, the mercenaries have to purchase their own kit from civilian markets and the black market. The resulting patchwork rigs may not be as solid as issued gear, yet, a lot more comfortable than a government tender.</entitydescription.pmc_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_pmc_vest>PMC lightweight bulletproof chest-rig</entityname.tsm_pmc_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_pmc_vest>Even if they’re only quasi-military, the mercs know exactly what the job needs. A cottage industry has come up to serve them, so they can piece together a bulletproof chest-rig with military protection level, along with a standardized pouches on it.</entitydescription.tsm_pmc_vest>
  <entityname.pmc_uniform1>PMC Combat Uniform</entityname.pmc_uniform1>
  <entitydescription.pmc_uniform1>This is a full of street fashion sense. The hooded jacket on the upper body is simple yet stylish, and the side stripes add a dynamic touch to the whole. It's suitable for activities in urban neighborhoods, being both comfortable and able to show one's personality. The casual pants with patterns are full of fashion elements, and the loose version allows for unrestricted movement. The classic sneakers balance fashion and practicality, and can provide good foot support and a comfortable experience for characters who shuttle in the city and perform special tasks. It's an excellent choice for wandering in the city and highlighting a unique style.</entitydescription.pmc_uniform1>
  <entityname.pmc_uniform2>PMC Combat Uniform</entityname.pmc_uniform2>
  <entitydescription.pmc_uniform2>It features a camouflage combat uniform, matched with protective gears like shoulder pads and arm guards. There is a tactical pouch on the waist. The overall appearance is full of a combat vibe, suitable for carrying out missions in complex environments.</entitydescription.pmc_uniform2>
  <entityname.tsm_boonie_hat>Boonie Hat</entityname.tsm_boonie_hat>
  <entitydescription.tsm_boonie_hat>It adopts a suitable light brown color and a wide-brimmed bucket hat design, which can effectively block the sun. Although there is no sun under the ice layer of Europa, making the sun-shading practical function unavailable, its unique color and style add a different sense of fashion to the cold Europa scene. It focuses on appearance and is a good choice for those who pursue a stylish look.</entitydescription.tsm_boonie_hat>
  <entityname.tsm_kl_hat>Reaper Tactical Hood</entityname.tsm_kl_hat>
  <entitydescription.tsm_kl_hat>Overall, it is mainly in dark colors and decorated with skull elements, full of a sense of mystery and deterrence. It integrates tactical goggles to assist observation and also has a communication device for convenient instant contact. It seems like a messenger from the shadow of death, adding a strange combat aura to the user.</entitydescription.tsm_kl_hat>
  <entityname.tsm_mm_hat>Mercenary Communication Cap</entityname.tsm_mm_hat>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mm_hat>It is mainly khaki in color and equipped with professional communication headsets, which ensure information transmission in complex battlefield environments. The matching goggles and face shield balance communication and protection, making it a reliable piece of equipment for mercenary communication personnel.</entitydescription.tsm_mm_hat>
  <entityname.tsm_mm2_hat>Mercenary Special Ops Protective Helmet</entityname.tsm_mm2_hat>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mm2_hat>It features black as its main color and is equipped with noise-canceling headphones, which can block out loud noises on the battlefield and help the wearer focus on key information. The red goggles have special optical effects, supporting observation in different light conditions, while the face shield protects the face. Together, they form a safe and efficient head protection system for mercenary special operations personnel.</entitydescription.tsm_mm2_hat>
  <!--装备：奇迹之海-->
  <entityname.tsm_outpost_police>Outpost Police Uniform</entityname.tsm_outpost_police>
  <entitydescription.tsm_outpost_police>A symbol of T.S.M's order, combining comfort with clear law enforcement visibility.</entitydescription.tsm_outpost_police>
  <entityname.tsm_outpost_police_vest>Outpost Police Body Armor</entityname.tsm_outpost_police_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_outpost_police_vest>Designed exclusively for daily security patrols, it only provides basic protection against close-range low-caliber weapon fire and fragmentation damage. Its lightweight build is optimized for prolonged patrols and crowd control duties, rather than withstanding high-intensity combat. After all, the primary mission of station police officers is to maintain order, not to engage in battlefield confrontations.</entitydescription.tsm_outpost_police_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_old_uniform>TSM Old-style Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_old_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_old_uniform>TSM Old-style combat uniform，Though it doesn't match the performance of the new combat uniforms from various departments, its affordability and durability still make it a favorite among most tacticians.</entitydescription.tsm_old_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_old_vest>TSM Old-style Bulletproof Vest</entityname.tsm_old_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_old_vest>It offers protection to more areas than a regular bulletproof vest, but its protective performance isn't particularly good.</entitydescription.tsm_old_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_advanced_uniform>Advanced Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_advanced_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_advanced_uniform>Uniform of the Advanced Combat Division</entitydescription.tsm_advanced_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_sundawn_uniform>The "Sunset Mountain" Security Uniform</entityname.tsm_sundawn_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_sundawn_uniform>A common combat suit in TSM station,mainly used by The "Sunset Mountain" combat division</entitydescription.tsm_sundawn_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_ballisticplate_vest>TSM Plate Insert Bulletproof Vest</entityname.tsm_ballisticplate_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_ballisticplate_vest>A bulletproof vest modified by "JiuZhou" Arsenal, with added plate slots that allow for the insertion of corresponding plates to protect against specific types of damage.</entitydescription.tsm_ballisticplate_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_heavy_vest>TSM New-style Bulletproof Vest</entityname.tsm_heavy_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_heavy_vest>The bulletproof vest issued by TSM to cope with more complex environments offers enhanced protection without impeding the soldiers' mobility. It also features more tactical attachment points.</entitydescription.tsm_heavy_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_mingfu_uniform>Ming Fu Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_mingfu_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mingfu_uniform>A combat uniform especially designed for the Ming Fu Squad, featuring lots of decorative elements and patterns that are both easy to work with and highly functional. It is amazingly durable, wear-resistant, and extremely comfortable. Hidden beneath the patterns are discreet pockets capable of holding several magazines or grenades.</entitydescription.tsm_mingfu_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_mingfu_vest>Ming Fu lightweight bulletproof chest-rig</entityname.tsm_mingfu_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mingfu_vest>The Ming Fu squad's gear is rather distinctive: besides a lightweight bulletproof chest-rig that never hinders movement, each operator is issued additional arm and leg protections. That set allows any other units pick out the squad from every other T.S.M. unit at a single glance.</entitydescription.tsm_mingfu_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_medic_helmet>Guard Corps Combat Uniform Helmet</entityname.tsm_medic_helmet>
  <entitydescription.tsm_medic_helmet>A dedicated slot for medical scanners is reserved;installing medical scanning accessories will activate the medical scanning interface.</entitydescription.tsm_medic_helmet>
  <entityname.tsm_jz_uniform>"JiuZhou" Combat Suit</entityname.tsm_jz_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_jz_uniform>Suit for "JiuZhou" Combat Division.The uniform has been reinforced to better resist blunt force trauma and bites. It also features carrying pouches that can hold some equipment, and it provides a comfortable fit.</entitydescription.tsm_jz_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_jz_helmet>"JiuZhou" Combat Helmet</entityname.tsm_jz_helmet>
  <entitydescription.tsm_jz_helmet>The Jiuzhou Combat Division Standard Helmet is based on an advanced combat helmet and has been modified to include a built-in night vision device that requires power to activate.</entitydescription.tsm_jz_helmet>
  <entityname.tsm_jz_vest>Jiuzhou Combat Armor</entityname.tsm_jz_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_jz_vest>The Jiuzhou Combat Division Standard Armor is based on advanced combat armor and requires regular maintenance to ensure sufficient protective effectiveness.</entitydescription.tsm_jz_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_riotcontrol_helmet>TSM Riotcontrol Helmet</entityname.tsm_riotcontrol_helmet>
  <entitydescription.tsm_riotcontrol_helmet>It can effectively prevent both civilian weapons and bladed weapons from harming the wearer's head. A large ballistic visor can be inserted to provide better protection.</entitydescription.tsm_riotcontrol_helmet>
  <entityname.tsm_heavycombat_helmet>TSM Heavycombat Helmet</entityname.tsm_heavycombat_helmet>
  <entitydescription.tsm_heavycombat_helmet>The lining has been thickened to offer stronger resistance to impacts, and a large ballistic visor can be inserted for enhanced protection.</entitydescription.tsm_heavycombat_helmet>
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_respirator>TSM Heavy Gas Mask</entityname.tsm_helmet_respirator>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_respirator>The matte black reinforced shell is embedded with a radiation-resistant coating, which can mitigate low-to-moderate intensity radiation exposure. Its lightweight frame also provides basic impact protection, making this helmet a common sight across various departments.</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_respirator>
  <entityname.tsm_helmet_outpost_combat>TSM "NuJiang" Combat Helmet</entityname.tsm_helmet_outpost_combat>
  <entitydescription.tsm_helmet_outpost_combat>This is the exclusive helmet of the Station Assault Squadron. Its all-black shell aligns with the squadron’s assault operational positioning, and the external night-vision module is its core identifier—this device allows team members to accurately acquire targets in low-light environments. During pitch-black assault missions, the Station Assault Squadron serves as the key force to breach enemy defensive lines.</entitydescription.tsm_helmet_outpost_combat>
  <entityname.lm_mingfu_helmet>Ming Fu Combat Helmet</entityname.lm_mingfu_helmet>
  <entitydescription.lm_mingfu_helmet>The helmet’s main frame is forged from matte black titanium alloy, with etched dark patterns on its surface serving as the identity mark for squad members. Its modular interfaces are compatible with a full spectrum of accessories—including thermal imagers, night-vision goggles, and medical panels—and can even connect to small protective face shields to enhance survivability in harsh environments.
    Redundant lightweight design has been discarded; instead, thickened lining and shock-absorbing modules balance protection and mobility. While slightly bulky in routine missions, this "Ming Fu Shell" can shield operatives from close-range shrapnel and stray rounds during high-intensity firefights.
    \nThe first slot can hold items:Thermal goggles for helmets/Night vision device for helmets/Helmet medical display screen/Ballistic visor for helmet（Heavy）.\nThe second slot can hold items:Identification device for helmet\nPress Alt + G for quick activation of helmet function.</entitydescription.lm_mingfu_helmet>
  <entityname.tsm_fast_helmet_headset>T.S.M Assault Communication Helmet</entityname.tsm_fast_helmet_headset>
  <entitydescription.tsm_fast_helmet_headset>Equipped with a set of radio headphones, allowing the voices of officers and peers to be transmitted more quickly to the soldiers' ears. Combined with a modular design, various helmet accessories can be inserted to jaw more tactical options.\nThe first slot can hold items: Ballistic visor for helmet, Thermal goggles for helmets/Night vision device for helmets/Helmet medical display screen）.\nThe second slot can hold items: Jaw protetor for helmets/Helmet Diving Mask.\nThe third slot can hold item:Identification device for helmet.\nPress Alt + G for quick activation of helmet function.</entitydescription.tsm_fast_helmet_headset>
  <entityname.tsm_nujiang_uniform>TSM "NuJiang" Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_nujiang_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_nujiang_uniform>This combat uniform boasts outstanding protective performance, yet its design has long been criticized by users. While its cut can be described as "function-oriented", its actual appearance is highly similar to the work clothes worn by plumbers and electricians in civilian settings. For this reason, whenever the Station Assault Squadron deploys for a mission, you can often hear the team members joking around: "Are we heading out to unclog the drains at some station again this time?"</entitydescription.tsm_nujiang_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_niaochao_uniform>Bird Nest Squadron Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_niaochao_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_niaochao_uniform>The exclusive combat uniform of the "Bird Nest" elite squadron affiliated with the Advanced Operations Department. Its unique blue-and-white striped camouflage serves as the key identifying feature. Designed to adapt to large-scale, high-intensity combat, the uniform integrates the characteristics of certain load-bearing equipment, with additional load-bearing pockets added to facilitate team members in storing magazines or emergency medical supplies.</entitydescription.tsm_niaochao_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_niaochao_vest>Bird Nest Squadron Plate Carrier</entityname.tsm_niaochao_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_niaochao_vest>The heavy full-coverage plate carrier used by the "Bird Nest" Squadron, specifically designed for large-scale, high-intensity combat. It is an indispensable piece of defense for the "Bird Nest" Squadron. While some argue that this plate carrier imposes significant restrictions on personnel mobility and performance in non-combat scenarios, such limitations are still acceptable compared to the protective performance it provides.</entitydescription.tsm_niaochao_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_niaochao_helmet>Bird Nest Squadron Helmet</entityname.tsm_niaochao_helmet>
  <entitydescription.tsm_niaochao_helmet>Based on a heavy combat helmet design, it offers excellent protective performance for the wearer while featuring certain tactical expansion capabilities. It can be equipped with a thermal imaging chip to provide the wearer with tactical advantages. However, it has drawbacks such as vision obstruction, making it suitable only for special operations personnel who require head protection and have specific tactical needs in high-intensity combat.</entitydescription.tsm_niaochao_helmet>
  <entityname.tsm_common_uniform>Jiuzhou Operations Department Service Uniform</entityname.tsm_common_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_common_uniform>Standard issue uniform from Jiuzhou Operations Department</entitydescription.tsm_common_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_kepuniform>San ShenQiu Combat Uniform</entityname.tsm_kepuniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_kepuniform>San ShenQiu, as an experimental team of operators, has been designed a dedicated combat system by the headquarters, which can only be activated when paired with the San ShenQiu Combat Helmet and Cape.</entitydescription.tsm_kepuniform>
  <entityname.tsm_kepcape>San ShenQiu Cape</entityname.tsm_kepcape>
  <entitydescription.tsm_kepcape>A dedicated cape for the San ShenQiu experimental team, specially designed to withstand certain amounts of damage and to resist damage caused by Triton rounds. It can activate an auxiliary system when paired with the San ShenQiu Combat Uniform and Helmet.</entitydescription.tsm_kepcape>
  <entityname.tsm_kepcap>San ShenQiu Combat Helmet</entityname.tsm_kepcap>
  <entitydescription.tsm_kepcap>A dedicated combat helmet for the San ShenQiu team, offering a certain level of defense and compatible with chips. It can activate an auxiliary system when paired with the combat uniform and cape.</entitydescription.tsm_kepcap>
  <entityname.tsm_advisers_vest>'Feline' Advisor Bulletproof Vest</entityname.tsm_advisers_vest>
  <entitydescription.tsm_advisers_vest>Bulletproof plates made from alien minerals, offering higher protection without hindering the operators' mobility.</entitydescription.tsm_advisers_vest>
  <entityname.tsm_advisers_mask>'Feline' Advisor Disguise Mask</entityname.tsm_advisers_mask>
  <entitydescription.tsm_advisers_mask>A mask issued for the advisory team's field missions, effectively concealing their identities.</entitydescription.tsm_advisers_mask>
  <entityname.tsm_advisers_uniform>'Feline' Advisor Uniform</entityname.tsm_advisers_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_advisers_uniform>The most professional team, reasonably priced, and fair to all. Feline Advisors are always on the front line, providing the best service.</entitydescription.tsm_advisers_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_65_uniform>65-Style Military Uniform</entityname.tsm_65_uniform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_65_uniform>百战新师惊贼胆，三年苦斗献吾身</entitydescription.tsm_65_uniform>
  <entityname.tsm_65_hat>65-Style Military Cap</entityname.tsm_65_hat>
  <entitydescription.tsm_65_hat>潇潇夜雨洗兵马，殷殷热血固金瓯</entitydescription.tsm_65_hat>
  <entityname.tsm_63_gear>63-Style Load-Bearing Gear</entityname.tsm_63_gear>
  <entitydescription.tsm_63_gear>此去泉合招旧部，旌旗十万斩阎罗</entitydescription.tsm_63_gear>
  <entityname.Extra_hat_male_tsm>Chief Officer's Hat</entityname.Extra_hat_male_tsm>
  <entitydescription.Extra_hat_male_tsm>The last piece of conscience, the last balance of order</entitydescription.Extra_hat_male_tsm>
  <entityname.tsm_suit_white>white suit</entityname.tsm_suit_white>
  <entitydescription.tsm_suit_white>Your second layer of skin, enveloping power and confidence</entitydescription.tsm_suit_white>
  <entityname.tsm_suit_brown>brown suit</entityname.tsm_suit_brown>
  <entitydescription.tsm_suit_brown>Your second layer of skin, enveloping power and confidence</entitydescription.tsm_suit_brown>
  <entityname.tsm_gendarmerie_uniforms>T.S.M Gendarmerie Uniform</entityname.tsm_gendarmerie_uniforms>
  <entitydescription.tsm_gendarmerie_uniforms>The gendarmerie uniform of T.S.M, mainly maintains troop discipline and ensures the execution of orders</entitydescription.tsm_gendarmerie_uniforms>
  <entityname.tsm_gendarmerie_hat>T.S.M Gendarmerie Hat</entityname.tsm_gendarmerie_hat>
  <entitydescription.tsm_gendarmerie_hat>Violations of rules and discipline will be severely punished without leniency.</entitydescription.tsm_gendarmerie_hat>
  <entityname.rz_prototype>RongZhuang Prototype</entityname.rz_prototype>
  <entitydescription.rz_prototype>Due to various reasons and the increasingly severe situation, the TSM headquarters urgently needed a heavy fire support platform capable of entering the interior of a submarine. Thus, the prototype of the heavy fire support platform named "RongZhuang" was born.</entitydescription.rz_prototype>
  <entityname.tsm_gtp_suit>Gravitational Traction Protective Suit</entityname.tsm_gtp_suit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_gtp_suit>Effectively resists the gravitational suppression produced by anti-gravity traction laser beams and can dive up to a maximum depth of 7,000 meters.</entitydescription.tsm_gtp_suit>
  <entityname.tsm_map_suit>Military Advanced Protective Suit</entityname.tsm_map_suit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_map_suit>This military-grade protective suit, primarily equipped by the Advanced Combat Division in the TSM, can adapt to many harsh environments. When paired with magnetic shoes, it allows the wearer to maintain their posture under minor flood impacts and can dive up to a maximum depth of 6,000 meters.</entitydescription.tsm_map_suit>
  <entityname.tsm_ow_suit>Orange Wraith Hazard Suit</entityname.tsm_ow_suit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_ow_suit>This hazard suit is exclusive to the Orange Wraith — as a full-scenario survival gear, its modular design covers core areas (torso, limbs, head) with corrosion-resistant, radiation-shielding composites, plus thermal insulation and cushioning layers. It fends off toxic gases, radioactive dust, and sustains life support in high-temperature/low-pressure extremes.
    A built-in self-injection slot adds an extra layer of safety in perilous environments, allowing quick access to emergency supplies (e.g. antidotes, stimulants) without exposing the wearer.
    Built on "single-suit multi-hazard compatibility", it handles industrial leaks, abandoned area infiltration, and low-intensity contaminated zone ops without modifications. The orange-red accents boost visibility while matching the Orange Wraith's signature insignia — a versatile, tactically distinct standard gear for high-risk environments. Maximum dive depth: 7,500 meters.</entitydescription.tsm_ow_suit><entityname.tsm_cep_suit>Class I Exposure Protective Suit</entityname.tsm_cep_suit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_cep_suit>Modified from a military protective suit, the creator has incorporated advanced life and biological support technologies. Special fibers can effectively separate the wearer from harsh environments. The helmet is equipped with night vision, significantly enhancing its functionality. Specialized shoes can firmly grip the ground, reducing the impact of shocks, and it can dive up to a maximum depth of 7,500 meters.</entitydescription.tsm_cep_suit>
  <entityname.tsm_rap_suit>Riot Advancer Protective Suit</entityname.tsm_rap_suit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_rap_suit>As an assault-oriented heavy armor designed specifically for high-intensity conflicts, its core focus is on enhanced mobility and impact resistance: Fully constructed from high-toughness composite armor plates, it can withstand projectiles and blunt-force impacts in riot scenarios. Meanwhile, its lightweight frame allows the wearer to maintain an advancing rhythm even amid chaotic crowds, achieving the tactical goal of "forcibly pushing forward through riots."
    Its boots integrate small magnetic generators. When activated, they can adhere to surfaces on shallow water or slippery terrain, stabilizing the wearer’s center of gravity without compromising movement speed, allowing the user to sustain an assault posture even in complex environments.</entitydescription.tsm_rap_suit>
  <entityname.tsm_rz_3a>"Rongzhuang" Type 3A</entityname.tsm_rz_3a>
  <entitydescription.tsm_rz_3a>A heavy exoskeleton armor in full matte black, its bulky mecha-style structure wrapped in reinforced armor, with red patterns at the joints being the only bright visual accent in its stern appearance. Designed around the core of "firepower + protection", its outer alloy layer can withstand medium-to-heavy firepower impacts, while the built-in power module allows the wearer to easily carry heavy weapons — it is a tough piece of equipment in frontline assault missions that can act as both a "mobile bunker" and a "firepower turret".</entitydescription.tsm_rz_3a>
  <entityname.tsm_beret>Beret</entityname.tsm_beret>
  <entitydescription.tsm_beret></entitydescription.tsm_beret>
  <!--装备：木卫二联盟-->
  <entityname.lm_rapidreaction_helmet>Coalition Rapid Reaction Helmet</entityname.lm_rapidreaction_helmet>
  <entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_helmet>A helmet specifically designed for rapid reaction forces, capable of withstanding direct bullet impacts and featuring night vision capabilities. Remember to replace the batteries in time to maintain equipment and information superiority.</entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_helmet>
  <entityname.lm_rapidreaction_vest>Coalition Rapid Reaction Bulletproof Vest</entityname.lm_rapidreaction_vest>
  <entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_vest>A bulletproof vest specifically designed for the Coalition's special task forces. It is more durable than regular bulletproof vests and offers excellent ballistic protection. It has proven itself in the Secession War, saving the lives of numerous task force members.</entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_vest>
  <entityname.lm_rapidreaction_uniform>Coalition Rapid Reaction Combat Uniform</entityname.lm_rapidreaction_uniform>
  <entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_uniform>A combat uniform specifically designed for the Coalition's special task forces. Although it is not bulletproof, it is durable, warm, and features pockets that allow the wearer to carry more items.</entitydescription.lm_rapidreaction_uniform>
  <entityname.lm_fast_helmet>Coalition Assault Helmet</entityname.lm_fast_helmet>
  <entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet>A standard issue helmet distributed in large quantities to frontline soldiers. Its numerous attachment points offer a wide range of customization options.</entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet>
  <entityname.lm_heavy_helmet>Coalition Heavy Combat Helmet</entityname.lm_heavy_helmet>
  <entitydescription.lm_heavy_helmet>Equipped with a ballistic visor and chin guard for enhanced protection.</entitydescription.lm_heavy_helmet>
  <entityname.lm_fast_helmet_headset>Coalition Assault Communication Helmet</entityname.lm_fast_helmet_headset>
  <entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet_headset>Equipped with a set of radio headphones, allowing the voices of officers and peers to be transmitted more quickly to the soldiers' ears. Combined with a modular design, various helmet accessories can be inserted to jaw more tactical options.\nThe first slot can hold items: Ballistic visor for helmet, Thermal goggles for helmets/Night vision device for helmets/Helmet medical display screen）.\nThe second slot can hold items: Jaw protetor for helmets/Helmet Diving Mask.\nThe third slot can hold item:Identification device for helmet.\nPress Alt + G for quick activation of helmet function.</entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet_headset>
  <entityname.lm_fast_helmet_faceshield>Coalition Assault Helmet (Ballistic Visor)</entityname.lm_fast_helmet_faceshield>
  <entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet_faceshield>A large transparent ballistic visor is installed, providing protection to the normally vulnerable face. A large ballistic visor can be inserted for better protection.</entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet_faceshield>
  <entityname.lm_fast_helmet_thermalgoggles>Coalition Assault Helmet (Thermal Imaging)</entityname.lm_fast_helmet_thermalgoggles>
  <entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet_thermalgoggles>A standard helmet equipped with a head-mounted thermal imaging device. The excellent suspension system keeps the center of gravity unchanged. Remember to change the batteries frequently to keep the thermal imager operational.</entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet_thermalgoggles>
  <entityname.lm_fast_helmet_protectivejaw>Coalition Assault Helmet (Chin Guard)</entityname.lm_fast_helmet_protectivejaw>
  <entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet_protectivejaw>A communication headset with a chin guard, offering an additional level of protection to the wearer.</entitydescription.lm_fast_helmet_protectivejaw>
  <entityname.lm_beowulf_helmet>Coalition Beowulf Helmet</entityname.lm_beowulf_helmet>
  <entitydescription.lm_beowulf_helmet>The standard helmet equipped by the Beowulf squad. Its superior performance allows excellent soldiers to execute tactics and orders more confidently. A large ballistic visor can be inserted for better protection.</entitydescription.lm_beowulf_helmet>
  <entityname.lm_beowulf_uniform>Coalition Beowulf Combat Uniform</entityname.lm_beowulf_uniform>
  <entitydescription.lm_beowulf_uniform>Standard-issue Combat Uniform of Beowulf Squadron.Crafted from lightweight, wear-resistant fabric, this full-body ensemble shields all vital body regions without overly restricting tactical maneuverability. It excels at providing basic protection for daily patrol duties, while also being compatible with heavy-duty gear upgrades to meet the demands of high-threat combat scenarios. Truly a versatile, scalable tactical option that balances general utility and expansion capability.</entitydescription.lm_beowulf_uniform>
  <entityname.lm_occupation_helmet>Coalition Occupation Force Combat Helmet</entityname.lm_occupation_helmet>
  <entitydescription.lm_occupation_helmet>A helmet equipped with a chin guard and a large transparent protective visor, effectively providing ballistic and slash resistance, and reducing the risk of concussions from impacts.</entitydescription.lm_occupation_helmet>
  <entityname.lm_crosstalk_helmet>Coalition Crosstalk Squad Helmet</entityname.lm_crosstalk_helmet>
  <entitydescription.lm_crosstalk_helmet></entitydescription.lm_crosstalk_helmet>
  <entityname.lm_vest_pt>Coalition Bulletproof Vest</entityname.lm_vest_pt>
  <entitydescription.lm_vest_pt>A standard bulletproof vest with average performance, characterized by its minimal carrying pouches and design that does not restrict the soldier's movement.</entitydescription.lm_vest_pt>
  <entityname.lm_vest_elite>Coalition Elite Bulletproof Vest</entityname.lm_vest_elite>
  <entitydescription.lm_vest_elite>A bulletproof vest made from new materials, offering enhanced protective capabilities while maintaining the original design. However, it still features only a few carrying pouches.</entitydescription.lm_vest_elite>
  <entityname.lm_vest_beowulf>Coalition Beowulf Bulletproof Vest</entityname.lm_vest_beowulf>
  <entitydescription.lm_vest_beowulf>Beowulf Body Armor
    Highlighted by its top-tier defensive performance, it integrates reinforced hard armor plates and shock-resistant fabric, providing reliable protection against close-to-medium range small arms fire and fragmentation threats. It delivers robust survivability for vital body regions in high-risk firefight scenarios.
    Yet its design trade-offs are distinct: to balance portability and tactical agility, the protective coverage is concentrated on the core torso area, with no shielding for limbs, neck, or other extremities. This armor is ideally suited for fast-paced assault and infiltration missions — sacrificing full-body coverage for the dual enhancement of core survival and tactical efficiency.</entitydescription.lm_vest_beowulf>
  <entityname.lm_occupation_uniform>Coalition Occupation Force Combat Uniform</entityname.lm_occupation_uniform>
  <entitydescription.lm_occupation_uniform>The built-in armor components of this combat uniform shield all vital body regions, striking a perfect balance between protection and tactical mobility. Constructed from rugged, wear-resistant materials, it is optimized for mission scenarios such as occupied area patrols and stability maintenance operations. It stands as a standard-issue military ensemble that delivers both exceptional practicality and strong deterrence</entitydescription.lm_occupation_uniform>
  <entityname.lm_vest_occupation>Coalition Occupation Force Bulletproof Vest</entityname.lm_vest_occupation>
  <entitydescription.lm_vest_occupation>As a standard full-coverage heavy protective gear of the Occupying Forces, it’s designed around the core logic of "dead-zone-free hard protection":Constructed with multi-layer composite ballistic plates that cover critical areas including the torso, shoulders, neck, and limbs, it can effectively withstand direct rifle fire, fragmentation blasts, and even sustain close-range continuous small-arms suppression — achieving high-level full-body protective coverage.</entitydescription.lm_vest_occupation>
  <entityname.lm_stormyseas_uniform>Coalition Stormy Seas Combat Uniform</entityname.lm_stormyseas_uniform>
  <entitydescription.lm_stormyseas_uniform>A common combat uniform in the Coalition. Although it lacks magazine storage, its excellent quality control has ensured no negative reviews.</entitydescription.lm_stormyseas_uniform>。
  <entityname.lm_vest_outpost>Coalition Station Security Officer Body Armor</entityname.lm_vest_outpost>
  <entitydescription.lm_vest_outpost>Exclusive Core Protection Gear for Station Security Officers.The torso is reinforced with top-tier armor plates to shield vital areas. Equipped with multiple mounting points for tactical attachments, it is lightweight and non-bulky — robust enough to withstand sudden threats, yet unobtrusive enough for daily patrols. A practical standard-issue gear for station security teams.</entitydescription.lm_vest_outpost>
  <!--装备：反抗军-->
  <entityname.fkj_anonymous_uniform>Separatist Sharp Raider Combat Uniform</entityname.fkj_anonymous_uniform>
  <entitydescription.fkj_anonymous_uniform>A combat uniform made from new materials. It sacrifices a bit of ballistic protection in exchange for corrosion resistance and the ability to prevent major bleeding. Four large pockets allow the wearer to carry more ammunition. However, the glove issue remains unresolved, and it is still not recommended for the wearer to use medical supplies.</entitydescription.fkj_anonymous_uniform>
  <entityname.fkj_abyssrambler_uniform>Separatist Combat Uniform</entityname.fkj_abyssrambler_uniform>
  <entitydescription.fkj_abyssrambler_uniform>The standard combat uniform of the Separatists, made with sturdy materials and good quality. The sewn-on small pockets allow soldiers to carry personal items or ammunition. Due to the overly thick material of the gloves, it is not recommended for soldiers to use medical supplies.</entitydescription.fkj_abyssrambler_uniform>
  <entityname.fkj_yehuo_uniform>Wildfire Separatist Combat Uniform</entityname.fkj_yehuo_uniform>
  <entitydescription.fkj_yehuo_uniform>An excellent combat uniform with a very good wearing experience. For some unknown reason, the wearer appears clumsy when using tools.</entitydescription.fkj_yehuo_uniform>
  <entityname.fkj_fast_helmet>Separatist Assault Helmet</entityname.fkj_fast_helmet>
  <entitydescription.fkj_fast_helmet>A standard helmet with barely acceptable performance, but the designer has preset a bunch of slots for customization and upgrades.</entitydescription.fkj_fast_helmet>
  <entityname.fkj_fast_helmet_reinforce>Separatist Reinforced Assault Helmet</entityname.fkj_fast_helmet_reinforce>
  <entitydescription.fkj_fast_helmet_reinforce>It has added ear guards and replaced with better padding and shock absorption design, which can effectively reduce the probability of the wearer suffering from concussion due to violent collisions.</entitydescription.fkj_fast_helmet_reinforce>
  <entityname.fkj_fast_helmet_thermalgoggles>Separatist Thermal Imaging Helmet</entityname.fkj_fast_helmet_thermalgoggles>
  <entitydescription.fkj_fast_helmet_thermalgoggles>Equipped with a head-mounted thermal imaging device. Due to the shifted center of gravity, the helmet is not very stable after being hit, and the protective effect is slightly reduced. If you want to keep enjoying the convenience of thermal imaging, remember to change the batteries frequently.</entitydescription.fkj_fast_helmet_thermalgoggles>
  <entityname.fkj_Anonymous_helmet>Separatist Sharp Raider Helmet</entityname.fkj_Anonymous_helmet>
  <entitydescription.fkj_Anonymous_helmet>It has added ear guards and goggles, and uses a brand-new cushioning structure, allowing soldiers to effectively resist the Coalition's new ammunition. A small ballistic visor can be inserted for better protection.</entitydescription.fkj_Anonymous_helmet>
  <entityname.fkj_yehuo_helmet>Wildfire Separatist Combat Helmet</entityname.fkj_yehuo_helmet>
  <entitydescription.fkj_yehuo_helmet>A new full-protection helmet, providing the best protection for your head, including the chin! A small ballistic visor can be inserted for better protection.</entitydescription.fkj_yehuo_helmet>
  <entityname.fkj_heavy_helmet>Separatist Elite Helmet</entityname.fkj_heavy_helmet>
  <entitydescription.fkj_heavy_helmet>A small ballistic visor can be inserted for better protection.</entitydescription.fkj_heavy_helmet>
  <entityname.fkj_vest_pt>Separatist Bulletproof Vest</entityname.fkj_vest_pt>
  <entitydescription.fkj_vest_pt>There's not much to say, it's just a standard Separatist bulletproof vest with a few carrying pouches for magazines and grenades.</entitydescription.fkj_vest_pt>
  <entityname.fkj_vest_elite>Separatist Elite Bulletproof Vest</entityname.fkj_vest_elite>
  <entitydescription.fkj_vest_elite>Based on the regular bulletproof vest, it has improved the internal design and material innovation, giving soldiers some resistance to the Coalition's new bullets. However, the carrying pouches are still limited.</entitydescription.fkj_vest_elite>
  <entityname.fkj_heavy_vest>Separatist Heavy Bulletproof Vest</entityname.fkj_heavy_vest>
  <entitydescription.fkj_heavy_vest>A thick bulletproof vest that gives the wearer a strong sense of security. With it on, you are the thickest meat shield in submarine alley warfare! (The Separatists advise you not to actually be a meat shield and to bring a shield.)</entitydescription.fkj_heavy_vest>
  <entityname.fkj_vest_yehuo>Wildfire Separatist Bulletproof Vest</entityname.fkj_vest_yehuo>
  <entitydescription.fkj_vest_yehuo>A bulletproof vest that only the elite of the Separatist elites can possess. The extensive use of new materials and excellent belt structure give this bulletproof vest very high ballistic resistance and bleeding resistance, even capable of withstanding the Coalition's new bullets.</entitydescription.fkj_vest_yehuo>
  <entityname.fkj_fast_helmet_headset>Separatist Assault Communication Helmet</entityname.fkj_fast_helmet_headset>
  <entitydescription.fkj_fast_helmet_headset>Equipped with a set of radio headphones, allowing the voices of officers and peers to be transmitted more quickly to the soldiers' ears. Combined with a modular design, various helmet accessories can be inserted to jaw more tactical options.\nThe first slot can hold items: Ballistic visor for helmet, Thermal goggles for helmets/Night vision device for helmets/Helmet medical display screen）.\nThe second slot can hold items: Jaw protetor for helmets/Helmet Diving Mask.\nThe third slot can hold item:Identification device for helmet.\nPress Alt + G for quick activation of helmet function.</entitydescription.fkj_fast_helmet_headset>
  <!--装备：降临派-->
  <entityname.adventists_uniform>Adventists' High Priest Robe</entityname.adventists_uniform>
  <entitydescription.adventists_uniform>A robe often worn by Adventists' leaders and chiefs, symbolizing their status. Surprisingly warm even under the cold ice.</entitydescription.adventists_uniform>
  <entityname.adventists_Wind_proof>Adventists' Windproof Jacket</entityname.adventists_Wind_proof>
  <entitydescription.adventists_Wind_proof></entitydescription.adventists_Wind_proof>
  <entityname.tsm_rz_pirent>RongZhuang Type Thief</entityname.tsm_rz_pirent>
  <entitydescription.tsm_rz_pirent>The original Type 2B machine, modified by the thief, with enhanced protective and output capabilities.</entitydescription.tsm_rz_pirent>
  <entityname.tsm_rz_pirent_k>RongZhuang Type Thief</entityname.tsm_rz_pirent_k>
  <entitydescription.tsm_rz_pirent_k>The original Type 2B machine, modified by the thief, with enhanced protective and output capabilities.</entitydescription.tsm_rz_pirent_k>
  <!-- 杂项 -->
  <entityname.tsm_soundplayer>Music Player</entityname.tsm_soundplayer>
  <entitydescription.tsm_soundplayer>Plays audio tapes obtained from creatures or purchased at outposts.</entitydescription.tsm_soundplayer>
  <entityname.CODE002>CODE:002</entityname.CODE002>
  <entitydescription.CODE002></entitydescription.CODE002>
  <entityname.zszg>True Coffin</entityname.zszg>
  <entitydescription.zszg></entitydescription.zszg>
  <entityname.bjzc>Tragic City Eloreno</entityname.bjzc>
  <entitydescription.bjzc></entitydescription.bjzc>
  <entityname.kl1>Charon One</entityname.kl1>
  <entitydescription.kl1>Tune audis pugnare?</entitydescription.kl1>
  <entityname.kl2>Charon Two</entityname.kl2>
  <entitydescription.kl2>Vere tu audis pugnare?</entitydescription.kl2>
  <entityname.tsm_daylight>Daylight Flare</entityname.tsm_daylight>
  <entitydescription.tsm_daylight>Lights up the surroundings as bright as daytime on Earth</entitydescription.tsm_daylight>
  <entityname.tsm_lm_lockbox>Coalition Weapon Blindbox</entityname.tsm_lm_lockbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lm_lockbox>An excellent lottery mechanism with no guaranteed reward.This is Barotruama\nOpen it by using Blindbox code（take by wreck）\nWhen durability reaches 0, use the right-click and left-click combination to open it.</entitydescription.tsm_lm_lockbox>
  <entityname.tsm_lm_lockbox>Coalition Weapon Blindbox</entityname.tsm_lm_lockbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lm_lockbox>It's time for the ten-roll draw.\nOpen it by using Blindbox code（take by wreck）\nWhen durability reaches 0, use the right-click and left-click combination to open it.</entitydescription.tsm_lm_lockbox>
  <entityname.tsm_fkj_lockbox>Separatists Weapon Blindbox</entityname.tsm_fkj_lockbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_fkj_lockbox>An excellent lottery mechanism with no guaranteed reward.This is Barotruama\nOpen it by using Blindbox code（take by wreck）\nWhen durability reaches 0, use the right-click and left-click combination to open it.</entitydescription.tsm_fkj_lockbox>
  <entityname.tsm_fkj_lockbox>Separatists Weapon Blindbox</entityname.tsm_fkj_lockbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_fkj_lockbox>It's time for the ten-roll draw.\nOpen it by using Blindbox code（take by wreck）\nWhen durability reaches 0, use the right-click and left-click combination to open it.</entitydescription.tsm_fkj_lockbox>
  <entityname.tsm_tsm_lockbox>T.S.M Weapon Blindbox</entityname.tsm_tsm_lockbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_tsm_lockbox>An excellent lottery mechanism with no guaranteed reward.This is Barotruama\nOpen it by using Blindbox code（take by wreck）\nWhen durability reaches 0, use the right-click and left-click combination to open it.</entitydescription.tsm_tsm_lockbox>
  <entityname.tsm_tsm_lockbox>T.S.M Weapon Blindbox</entityname.tsm_tsm_lockbox>
  <entitydescription.tsm_tsm_lockbox>It's time for the ten-roll draw.\nOpen it by using Blindbox code（take by wreck）\nWhen durability reaches 0, use the right-click and left-click combination to open it.</entitydescription.tsm_tsm_lockbox>
  <entityname.tsm_mh_licences>Blindbox code</entityname.tsm_mh_licences>
  <entitydescription.tsm_mh_licences>use to open Weapon Blindbox</entitydescription.tsm_mh_licences>
  <!--职业-->
  <jobname.tsm_soldier>Site Assault Trooper</jobname.tsm_soldier>
  <jobdescription.tsm_soldier>Belongs to the Advanced Combat Division of T.S.M</jobdescription.tsm_soldier>
  <!--阿糖-->
  <entityname.tsm_suger>Sugar's Transmogrifier</entityname.tsm_suger>
  <entitydescription.tsm_suger>Sugar's transmogrifier, can transform into Sugar's appearance</entitydescription.tsm_suger>
  <entityname.suger_combat_uniform>Sugar's Combat Suit</entityname.suger_combat_uniform>
  <entitydescription.suger_combat_uniform>Uses a durable bulletproof synthetic fiber to protect vulnerable areas, but heavily tailored for flexibility. Strangely, the outfit includes an old captain's jacket that looks oversized and worn, which, according to Sugar, symbolizes "responsibility and duty."</entitydescription.suger_combat_uniform>
  <entityname.suger_clothes>Sugar's Hoodie</entityname.suger_clothes>
  <entitydescription.suger_clothes>A hoodie that Sugar often wears while resting, light and comfortable</entitydescription.suger_clothes>
  <entityname.suger_boardingaxe>‖color:159,207,217,255‖'Suger's Battle Axe'‖color:end‖</entityname.suger_boardingaxe>
  <entitydescription.suger_boardingaxe>‖color:159,207,217,255‖Swing towards the enemy, and also towards one's former self.‖color:end‖</entitydescription.suger_boardingaxe>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_Icarus>‖color:159,207,217,255‖Hand Cannon Icarus‖color:end‖</entityname.tsmmissions_Icarus>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_Icarus>‖color:159,207,217,255‖Suger's sidearm, a rotary pistol with integrated flashlight and grenade launcher, fires regular handcannon rounds. It was gifted by Commander Lerentine when Suger joined TSM, and has remained reliable through battles large and small. No one knows how a man of Suger's stature can single-handedly operate a pistol of this horrendously large caliber.\n\n“In mid-air, the wax of hypocrisy melted under the sun, and Icarus crashed into the sea”‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsmmissions_Icarus>
  <!--莱伦汀-->
  <entityname.tsm_grey_pupils>‖color:221,106,29,255‖Gray Eyes‖color:end‖</entityname.tsm_grey_pupils>
  <entitydescription.tsm_grey_pupils>‖color:221,106,29,255‖Lerentine's sidearm, uses hand cannon rounds\nIt is said to be her squad leader's gun from when she was part of the Advanced Operations Department. During an ambush, the leader was shot and killed while saving her. She then took the gun, donned the leader's helmet, and gave the orders.\nShe became known as the "Child of Doom," TSM's child, and your last savior when death looms over you.‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_grey_pupils>
  <entityname.tsm_lerentine>Lerentine's Transmogrifier</entityname.tsm_lerentine>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lerentine>Lerentine's transmogrifier, can transform into Lerentine's appearance</entitydescription.tsm_lerentine>
  <entityname.tsm_lerentine_zhong>‖color:221,106,29,255‖Mound‖color:end‖</entityname.tsm_lerentine_zhong>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lerentine_zhong>‖color:221,106,29,255‖Born with a shadow that does not follow my form, and in death my soul does not connect with my dreams‖color:end‖</entitydescription.tsm_lerentine_zhong>
  <!--幻下琅-->
  <entityname.tsmmissions_px18_pistols>‖color:150,0,0,255‖PX-18‖color:end‖</entityname.tsmmissions_px18_pistols>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_px18_pistols>Uses a‖color:150,0,0,255‖9mm‖color:end‖pistol magazine</entitydescription.tsmmissions_px18_pistols>
  <entityname.hxl_knife>‖color:150,0,0,255‖Illusion‖color:end‖</entityname.hxl_knife>
  <entitydescription.hxl_knife>‖color:150,0,0,255‖A False Reality‖color:end‖</entitydescription.hxl_knife>
  <entityname.tsm_hxl>Huan Xia Lang Device</entityname.tsm_hxl>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hxl>Lang's Headphones, Can Morph Into Lang</entitydescription.tsm_hxl>
  <entityname.tsm_hxl_unform>Clothes of Phantom Lang</entityname.tsm_hxl_unform>
  <entitydescription.tsm_hxl_unform>Lang\nEntity under the Phantom</entitydescription.tsm_hxl_unform>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_hx870>Disillusion 870</entityname.tsmmissions_hx870>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_hx870>Smile more</entitydescription.tsmmissions_hx870>
  <entityname.tsmmissions_hxl_ju>Gloom</entityname.tsmmissions_hxl_ju>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_hxl_ju>Grieve less</entitydescription.tsmmissions_hxl_ju>
  <!--妖梦-->
  <entityname.tsmmissions_TTI2011>‖color:100,0,0,255‖TTI2011‖color:end‖</entityname.tsmmissions_TTI2011>
  <entitydescription.tsmmissions_TTI2011>The only heirloom left by her Father, uses‖color:100,0,0,255‖9mm‖color:end‖ pistol magazines.</entitydescription.tsmmissions_TTI2011>
  <entityname.tsm_youmu>Youmu Device</entityname.tsm_youmu>
  <entitydescription.tsm_youmu></entitydescription.tsm_youmu>
  <!--林荷音-->
  <entityname.tsm_lin>Lin Heiyin Transmogrifier</entityname.tsm_lin>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lin/>
  <entityname.tsm_pucs_light>Lightweight Piezoelectric PUCS Exosuit</entityname.tsm_pucs_light>
  <entitydescription.tsm_pucs_light>A PUCS diving suit modified by Lin Heiyin, replacing the alloy armor sections with lighter advanced composites. The weight reduction allows the wearer far greater agility without reducing protection, withstanding pressures down to 7,500 m. A Lin HeYin designed electro-shock active-defense system is built into the back and helmet, insert a battery to activate the piezoelectric defenses.</entitydescription.tsm_pucs_light>
  <entityname.tsm_insulated_suit>Insulated Inner Suit</entityname.tsm_insulated_suit>
  <entitydescription.tsm_insulated_suit>A one-piece skin-tight suit made of insulating rubber with grounding wires—Heiyin’s everyday essential for live-electrical work. Originally white, it was switched to black after Yan told her black is slimming. Lately, Heiyin’s appetite has been a bit way more excellent, so the faux muscle texture printed on the belly now looks really hilarious. Stare at her tummy and she’ll definitely come at you with a wrench.</entitydescription.tsm_insulated_suit>
  <entityname.tsm_insulated_suit_ai>Insulated Inner Suit</entityname.tsm_insulated_suit_ai>
  <entitydescription.tsm_insulated_suit_ai>A one-piece skin-tight suit made of insulating rubber with grounding wires—Heiyin’s everyday essential for live-electrical work. Originally white, it was switched to black after Yan told her black is slimming. Lately, Heiyin’s appetite has been a bit way more excellent, so the faux muscle texture printed on the belly now looks really hilarious. Stare at her tummy and she’ll definitely come at you with a wrench.</entitydescription.tsm_insulated_suit_ai>
  <entityname.tsm_lin_tool>Piezoelectric Launcher</entityname.tsm_lin_tool>
  <entitydescription.tsm_lin_tool>A multi-function tool Lin Heiyin poured tons of effort into. It welds, cuts, and also incorporates a prototype steam cannon and a fission sniper mode. Requires fuel rods and a battery to operate.（no ai use）</entitydescription.tsm_lin_tool>
  <tsm_lin_t1>An anxious looking engineer stopped you./nHey！Was the submarine that just docked yours?？</tsm_lin_t1>
  <tsm_lin_t2>I detected that T034 is active in the nearby waters. By coincidence, my submarine is under maintenance and can't move. Could you possibly help me out...</tsm_lin_t2>
  <tsm_lin_t4>Please let me explain... After the 034 experimental accident, T037 has regained its sanity and is still in a weakened state. It still has some kind of device left by Dr. Lin Han on its body. If we can investigate it further, I think humanity will soon be able to conquer it... I know sailors don't like these empty promises, but I've already prepared the reward, and I'll provide you with insulating diving suits. Plzzzz.</tsm_lin_t4>
  <tsm_lin_t5>That's right... He devoted his entire life to T037, tormenting himself in the process, and in the end, he was destroyed by it—both in life and in reputation. I just want to finish the journey he never completed.</tsm_lin_t5>
  <tsm_lin_t6>I will send the insulating tech diving suits to the submarine's cargo hold before you set off. Remember to throw some flares or other luminous objects to distract it. Although it is in a weakened state now, do not let your guard down. Defeat T034, remove the suspicious device from it, and I will be waiting for your good news at the next station. I salute you.</tsm_lin_t6>
  <tsm_lin_p1>Yes,what?</tsm_lin_p1>
  <tsm_lin_p2>You mean T037?! No way, that thing almost wiped out all of humanity on Europa before. There's no way we're going to commit suicide for you!</tsm_lin_p2>
  <tsm_lin_p3>Dr. Lin Han? Let me guess, you're his daughter, Lin Heyin?</tsm_lin_p3>
  <tsm_lin_p4>Alright... You scientists, though always making mistakes, are the ones we have to rely on to lead human civilization forward. What should I do?</tsm_lin_p4>
  <tsm_lin_t11>Congratulations! Did you manage to retrieve the suspicious device from T034?</tsm_lin_t11>
  <tsm_lin_t12>It's a pity... But as long as you're safe, that's what matters. Well done, everyone.</tsm_lin_t12>
  <tsm_lin_t13>He was just trying to communicate with T034 using a brain - computer interface, but an accident happened... Now there's an incredible hypothesis: Dr. Lin Han might still be alive. He accidentally uploaded part of his consciousness into T034's brain, but it's extremely unstable... How could a human possibly adapt to a giant beast's body? So both he and T034 are in great pain now.</tsm_lin_t13>
  <tsm_lin_t14>This is just a hypothesis I deduced using a theoretical model. If this brain - computer interface port system can still be repaired and the operational logs inside can be retrieved, all the problems will be solved effortlessly... You've done me a great favor, and I can also lend a hand to your submarine. Leave the electrical work to me!</tsm_lin_t14>
  <tsm_lin_t15>This is... the brain - computer interface port system, and it's actually been preserved!</tsm_lin_t15>
  <tsm_lin_p11>It lost consciousness and sank into the abyss, and it was too deep. Our submarine hasn't regained its power yet. I'm sorry we didn't retrieve the device you needed.</tsm_lin_p11>
  <tsm_lin_p12>Brain - computer interface? So the rumors are true? Dr. Lin Han connected his consciousness to T037 using a brain - computer interface, which caused T037 to go berserk and almost made the people of Europa regress to Crawlers.</tsm_lin_p12>
  <tsm_lin_p13>This is madness! You should report this to the Coalition and the T.S.M. If it goes berserk again, many more people will die!</tsm_lin_p13>
  <tsm_lin_p14>I got it!</tsm_lin_p14>
  <tsm_lin_p15>You don't have it with you? Then I'll wait here for you. Please go and get it.</tsm_lin_p15>
  <!--燕-->
  <entityname.tsm_scarl>SCAR-L CQC Lightweight Assault Rifle</entityname.tsm_scarl>
  <entitydescription.tsm_scarl>Uses Coalition ‖color:0,200,0,255‖5.56‖color:end‖ magazines, cannot be equipped with drum magazines. One of Yan Shuting's custom sidearms, with an FN40GL grenade launcher attached and a shorter barrel for easier carrying, providing timely fire support when the advisory team encounters danger.</entitydescription.tsm_scarl>
  <entityname.tsm_usp45_pistols>USP45 Silenced Pistol</entityname.tsm_usp45_pistols>
  <entitydescription.tsm_usp45_pistols>Uses ‖color:0,200,0,255‖.45ACP‖color:end‖ pistol magazines. One of Yan Shuting's sidearms, with a small tactical flashlight attached underneath. Previously, the Feline Advisory Team had these pistols, but they were not favored due to insufficient power. Yan modified it to .45 caliber for close-quarters self-defense against unarmored targets in narrow environments.</entitydescription.tsm_usp45_pistols>
  <entityname.tsm_m200>M200 "Intervener" Prototype Precision Sniper Rifle</entityname.tsm_m200>
  <entitydescription.tsm_m200>Uses ‖color:0,200,0,255‖10.36*77‖color:end‖ sniper rifle magazines. Yan's primary sidearm, a gift from a friend when she joined the Feline Advisory Team. It is said that there is only one of these in Europa. The precision machining technology is one of the main difficulties. But more importantly, in the battles of Europa, there are few situations where high-precision, long-range sniper rifles are needed, except for the Feline Advisory Team. This legendary sniper rifle, which can hit an oxygen tank from a kilometer away, has silently taken the lives of many overconfident individuals.</entitydescription.tsm_m200>
  <entityname.tsm_1036_77_mag>Sniper Rifle Magazine (10.36*77)</entityname.tsm_1036_77_mag>
  <entitydescription.tsm_1036_77_mag>Contains 7 standard 10.3*77 caliber sniper rifle bullets</entitydescription.tsm_1036_77_mag>
  <entityname.tsm_yan>Yan</entityname.tsm_yan>
  <entityname.tsm_pifu>Pi Fu</entityname.tsm_pifu>
  <charactername.tsm_yan>Yan</charactername.tsm_yan>
  <npctitle.tsm_yan>"Feline" Military Advisor</npctitle.tsm_yan>
  <entityname.tsm_yan_item1>Yan's notes-part one</entityname.tsm_yan_item1>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yan_item1>This is one of the notes from Yan,You can recruit her as long as you have gathered all four notes</entitydescription.tsm_yan_item1>
  <entityname.tsm_yan_item2>Yan's notes-part two</entityname.tsm_yan_item2>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yan_item2>This is one of the notes from Yan,You can recruit her as long as you have gathered all four notes</entitydescription.tsm_yan_item2>
  <entityname.tsm_yan_item3>Yan's notes-part three</entityname.tsm_yan_item3>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yan_item3>This is one of the notes from Yan,You can recruit her as long as you have gathered all four notes</entitydescription.tsm_yan_item3>
  <entityname.tsm_yan_item4>Yan's notes-part four</entityname.tsm_yan_item4>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yan_item4>This is one of the notes from Yan,You can recruit her as long as you have gathered all four notes</entitydescription.tsm_yan_item4>
  <tsm_yan_t1>You're the crew from the sub just docked in?</tsm_yan_t1>
  <tsm_yan_t2>You and your crew are treating the gunshot from your back.No need to think Your combat coordination is a complete mess.</tsm_yan_t2>
  <tsm_yan_t3>Have your ever heard of T.S.M "Feline" Military Consultant?I'm one of them,currently serve as a sniper.I can offer your crew the best military training with a little cost.Hmm，it seems like there is a discount recently,10000mk…never mind,7000mk! A cute girl will never lie to you isn't it?</tsm_yan_t3>
  <tsm_yan_t4>7000mk for the deal, I really can't offer you a cheaper price.</tsm_yan_t4>
  <tsm_yan_t_s1>Hmm? You know my name? Who are you?</tsm_yan_t_s1>
  <tsm_yan_t_s2>HAAA！I shouldn't have hesitated to tear them up. I like you, sailor with taste and discernment! As a matter of fact, I need to complete my internship on the submarine to earn my consulting qualification. So, seeing that you're my fan, I'll be magnanimous and offer free guidance on board.</tsm_yan_t_s2>
  <tsm_yan_t_f>You son of .....,stop right there! I swear I will kick your ass, for sure!</tsm_yan_t_f>
  <tsm_yan_p1>How can I help you?</tsm_yan_p1>
  <tsm_yan_p2>EEE...You are?</tsm_yan_p2>
  <tsm_yan_p3>Bargaining/n(Need to collect 4 of her papers,the same will be ok too）</tsm_yan_p3>
  <tsm_yan_p4>That's way too expensive!I could went to the HR and spend less money for a crew too</tsm_yan_p4>
  <tsm_yan_p_s1>You're Yan right?</tsm_yan_p_s1>
  <tsm_yan_p_s2>I found some discarded sketch comics at the station, and the author's self - portrait looks a lot like you. You must have been an artist before, right? I want to collect them. Compared to cold money, these works are truly priceless treasures!</tsm_yan_p_s2>
  <tsm_yan_p_f>This is a lot of money! Young lady, and... where can you find a sniper who wears glasses?</tsm_yan_p_f>
  <entityname.tsm_yan_jl>Yan Resume</entityname.tsm_yan_jl>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yan_jl></entitydescription.tsm_yan_jl>
  <entityname.tsm_yan_story>Yan'story</entityname.tsm_yan_story>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yan_story>It records some stories about Yan</entitydescription.tsm_yan_story>
  <entityname.tsm_yan_rp>Recorder</entityname.tsm_yan_rp>
  <entitydescription.tsm_yan_rp>Yan\n\nAt dawn, I dream of your birthday,\nLike a lamb rolling toward the east.\nAt dusk, I dream of my death,\nLike that lamb rolling toward the west.</entitydescription.tsm_yan_rp>
  <!--克里斯-->
  <npctitle.tsm_chris>Former Captain of the Beowulf Squad</npctitle.tsm_chris>
  <entityname.tsm_beowulf>Beowulf Medal</entityname.tsm_beowulf>
  <entitydescription.tsm_beowulf>A specially made medal for the Beowulf Squad by the Coalition, in recognition of their outstanding contributions to riot control and counter-terrorism over the years.</entitydescription.tsm_beowulf>
  <entityname.tsm_m7>Coalition M7 Battle Rifle</entityname.tsm_m7>
  <entitydescription.tsm_m7>Uses Coalition ‖color:0,200,0,255‖6.8*51‖color:end‖ magazines. The official version of the MCXspear, but only issued to senior officers of some elite units, Chris being one of them. The scratches on the buttstock record the fallen prey of the Beowulf Squad, sending chills down one's spine.</entitydescription.tsm_m7>
  <entityname.tsm_chris_jl>Chris Resume</entityname.tsm_chris_jl>
  <entitydescription.tsm_chris_jl></entitydescription.tsm_chris_jl>
  <entityname.tsm_rp>Recorder</entityname.tsm_rp>
  <entitydescription.tsm_rp>Chris Evans
    A moment brighter than tears</entitydescription.tsm_rp>
  <tsm_chris_c1>In the crowd, you spot someone very familiar. To confirm your guess, you run up and call out to him.
    "Have we met somewhere before?"
    As he turns around, your eyes immediately catch a grotesque and deep scar on his face—just as you suspected, he is indeed the former captain of the Beowulf Squad who was once wanted by the Coalition—Chris Evans.</tsm_chris_c1>
  <tsm_chris_p1>Despite his icy demeanor, there is still an imperceptible flicker in his eyes for a moment.</tsm_chris_p1>
  <tsm_chris_c2>His hand slowly reaches for his waist, as if the air would be ignited in the next second, suffocating. Your gazes intersect at this moment, the atmosphere suddenly solidifies, dropping to freezing point.
    "Hey! Don't be nervous," you raise your hands, palms out, slowly waving them, trying to break the tense atmosphere with a calm tone. Your movements are not large, for fear that any misstep would trigger an irreparable conflict.
    Chris stares at you, his hand resting on his waist, seemingly weighing the truth of your words. After a moment, he finally relaxes a bit, but still does not let his guard down completely.</tsm_chris_c2>
  <tsm_chris_p2>"Follow me," you whisper, nodding at him, then turn and walk towards a small passage.</tsm_chris_p2>
  <tsm_chris_c3>You lead him through several dim corridors until you reach a secluded corner—undisturbed by others and free from surveillance.
    "It's safe here. We can talk properly," you lean against the wall. "Abuse of power, violent private punishment, murder, disobedience of orders... all these charges are written under your name." Your voice is deep, each word piercing through the air and straight into his heart. "Now, when people on Europa talk about you, they talk about you as if you were the messenger of death. Seeing you, it seems that life will be taken away from them in the next second."
    Chris listens silently, lowering his head, taking out a crumpled cigarette from his pocket, slowly putting it to his lips, and lighting it with a lighter. The fire flickers in the dim corner, casting his face in an even darker shade. The deep scar looks particularly grotesque in the interplay of light and shadow, as if it were an indelible mark. He takes a deep drag, exhales slowly through his nostrils, enveloping himself in a cloud of smoke, carrying a heavy and cold sense of oppression. He raises his head, his gaze piercing through the smoke, looking straight at you, his eyes filled with a complex emotion, a mix of mockery and a silent warning.
    "Join me!" Your tone is firm. "Here, you will definitely be safe. The Coalition's wanted order, those hounds chasing you, cannot threaten you. Here, you can be free from being swallowed by their conspiracies and shackles." You take a small step forward, lowering your voice. "And it's not just protection—I can give you the chance to settle accounts with those evil people. Those who cause chaos and incite riots should not escape their deserved judgment!"
    When Chris hears the words "settle accounts with those evil people," a glimmer of light flashes in his originally indifferent eyes, as if igniting some long-buried emotion deep within him. He exhales a cloud of smoke, squints his eyes, and slowly speaks: "I don't care about the Coalition's wanted order. They've wanted to catch me for a long time." He pauses, his tone tinged with a hint of probing and disdain: "It's your mention of judgment that interests me a bit. But words are empty. Show something concrete. How do you prove that you have the strength to make me join?"
    "In this world, only those who are truly powerful have the right to talk about judgment and order. And you? What makes you qualified?"</tsm_chris_c3>
  <tsm_chris_p3>This is my proof (takes out the Beowulf Medal)</tsm_chris_p3>
  <tsm_chris_c_e1>How could you have it?</tsm_chris_c_e1>
  <tsm_chris_p_e>I never care about the process, only the result</tsm_chris_p_e>
  <tsm_chris_c_e2>Looks like you'll need to stock up on more lighters on your ship. Come on, Captain, let's start clearing out those guilty ones!</tsm_chris_c_e2>
  <tsm_chris_c_n>If you can't prove your strength, don't bother me!</tsm_chris_c_n>
  <!--ars-->
  <tsm.t1>Hello, I am an employee of ARS Company stationed at TSM. How can I assist you?</tsm.t1>
  <tsm.arsrw>I saw the bounty notice saying there are new missions, so I came to see if there is anything I can do</tsm.arsrw>
  <tsm.other>Hello, I was told there are some tricky missions now. I would like to hear about them</tsm.other>
  <tsm.ars.1>Sounds good</tsm.ars.1>
  <tsm.ars.11>If you accept, that's great. Go ahead, no matter the outcome</tsm.ars.11>
  <tsm.ars.2>Maybe not, I will not participate</tsm.ars.2>
  <tsm.ars.22>If you refuse, that's fine. I will find someone else</tsm.ars.22>
  <tsm.urgent>Let me check, just a moment</tsm.urgent>
  <tsm.urgent_save_yes>There is indeed an urgent matter now. Previously, a dangerous person in TSM hijacked someone in the shipping lane. We have just located their position through positioning, so we need manpower to rescue Miss Qiu</tsm.urgent_save_yes>
  <tsm.save_yes>Delighted to help!</tsm.save_yes>
  <tsm.save_yes_1>Great, the location has been sent to your terminal. There is no time to lose!</tsm.save_yes_1>
  <tsm.urgent_save_no>There are no tricky missions at the moment</tsm.urgent_save_no>

  <!--子分类-->
  <subcategory.tsmmissions>T.S.M. MISSIONS - T.S.M</subcategory.tsmmissions>
  <!--建筑-->
  <entityname.tsm_fog>Fog</entityname.tsm_fog>
  <entityname.tsm_slogan>Slogan of the T.S.M</entityname.tsm_slogan>
  <entityname.tsm_mech>T.S.M Mecha Decoration</entityname.tsm_mech>
  <entityname.tsm_bossitem>T.S.M Boss Drop Decoration</entityname.tsm_bossitem>
  <entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental>Evil Plague Flesh Decoration</entityname.tsm_eyi_ornamental>
  <entityname.tsm_hf>Propaganda Banner</entityname.tsm_hf>
  <!--天赋-->
  <talentname.tsm_ei_talent_test>Experimental Evil Plague Normal State</talentname.tsm_ei_talent_test>
  <talentname.tsm_ei_talent_stabilise>Stable Evil Plague Normal State</talentname.tsm_ei_talent_stabilise>
  <talentname.tsm_ei>Masterpiece</talentname.tsm_ei>
  <talentname.tsm_all_ru>Pure Evil Plague State</talentname.tsm_all_ru>
  <talentname.tsm_warlord>Warlord</talentname.tsm_warlord>
  <talentname.tsm_specops>Spec Ops</talentname.tsm_specops>
  <talentname.tsm_beatcop>Beat Cop</talentname.tsm_beatcop>
  <talentname.tsm_bleeding_outpost_sundown>Hemostatic Agent</talentname.tsm_bleeding_outpost_sundown>
  <talenttree.tsm_gunner>Gunner</talenttree.tsm_gunner>
  <talenttree.tsm_frogman>Frogman</talenttree.tsm_frogman>
  <talenttree.tsm_enforcer>Enforcer</talenttree.tsm_enforcer>
  <talenttree.tsm_outpostsecurityofficer_gunner>Gunner</talenttree.tsm_outpostsecurityofficer_gunner>
  <talenttree.tsm_outpostsecurityofficer_frogman>Frogman</talenttree.tsm_outpostsecurityofficer_frogman>
  <talenttree.tsm_outpostsecurityofficer_enforcer>Enforcer</talenttree.tsm_outpostsecurityofficer_enforcer>
  <talenttree.tsm_outpostsecurityofficer_primary>Primary</talenttree.tsm_outpostsecurityofficer_primary>
  <talentname.suger_tail_handle>Sugar-tail Transmogrifier</talentname.suger_tail_handle>
  <talentdescription.suger_tail_handle>When you wear the device, you will grow cat ears and a cat tail.</talentdescription.suger_tail_handle>
  <talentname.tsm_olympian>Olympian</talentname.tsm_olympian>
  <talentdescription.tsm_olympian>You can gain skill levels up to 200.</talentdescription.tsm_olympian>
  <talentname.tsm_vip_bodyguard>TSM VIP Bodyguard Enhancement</talentname.tsm_vip_bodyguard>
  <talentdescription.tsm_vip_bodyguard>Enhancements received by TSM Bodyguards for them to better perform their duty.</talentdescription.tsm_vip_bodyguard>
  <talentname.tsm_ai_outpost>Stable Evil Plague Normal State of T.S.M</talentname.tsm_ai_outpost>
  <talentdescription.tsm_ai_outpost>Alter part of the DNA sequence to make the body reject foreign parasites.</talentdescription.tsm_ai_outpost>
  <talentname.tsm_eyi_instability>Unstable Evil Plague Anomaly State</talentname.tsm_eyi_instability>
  <talentname.tsm_ai_asphyxiating_pressure>Golden Lion</talentname.tsm_ai_asphyxiating_pressure>
  <talentname.tsm_lightningwizard>Anti-Stab Armor</talentname.tsm_lightningwizard>
  <talentdescription.tsm_lightningwizard>When taking ranged damage, it will stun the attacker.</talentdescription.tsm_lightningwizard>
  <talentname.tsm_ai_stun>Strong Reaction</talentname.tsm_ai_stun>
  <talentname.tsm_operator_revolt>Riotous Advance</talentname.tsm_operator_revolt>
  <talentdescription.tsm_operator_revolt>When wearing Riotous Advance Protection Suits，and in possession of Electric baton and Round riot shield，increase ‖color:0,150,0,255‖40% of your stun and physical damage resistance、20% of your movementspeed and 200% of your attackspeed‖color:end‖ with a decrease of ‖color:0,200,0,255‖30% of your damage‖color:end‖</talentdescription.tsm_operator_revolt>
  <talentname.tsm_gunskill_mastery>Firearms Proficiency</talentname.tsm_gunskill_mastery>
  <talentdescription.tsm_gunskill_mastery>When you possess the talent, killing a certain number of creatures with weapons from different factions can grant you certain bonuses. Submachine guns belong to ‖color:245,215,15,255‖TSM‖color:end‖ weapons, pistols to ‖color:245,215,15,255‖Coalition‖color:end‖ weapons, and revolvers to ‖color:245,215,15,255‖Separatist‖color:end‖ weapons, ‖color:245,215,15,255‖the count is not reset upon death‖color:end‖.
    When you kill creatures with ‖color:245,215,15,255‖Coalition‖color:end‖ weapons:
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖25‖color:end‖ creatures reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖7% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using Coalition weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖50‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖5% weapon damage‖color:end‖ when using Coalition weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖75‖color:end‖ creatures reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖8% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using Coalition weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖100‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖5% weapon damage‖color:end‖ when using Coalition weapons.
    When you kill creatures with ‖color:245,215,15,255‖Separatist‖color:end‖ weapons:
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖25‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖7% weapon damage‖color:end‖ when using Separatist weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖50‖color:end‖ creatures reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖4% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using Separatist weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖75‖color:end‖ creatures reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖6% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using Separatist weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖100‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖8% weapon damage‖color:end‖ when using Splinter weapons.
    When you kill creatures with ‖color:245,215,15,255‖TSM‖color:end‖ weapons:
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖50‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖6% weapon damage‖color:end‖ and reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖6% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using TSM weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖100‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖6% weapon damage‖color:end‖, reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖6% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using TSM weapons.
  </talentdescription.tsm_gunskill_mastery>
  <talentname.tsm_gunskill_mastery_lm>Coalition Firearms Proficiency</talentname.tsm_gunskill_mastery_lm>
  <talentdescription.tsm_gunskill_mastery_lm>When you possess the talent, killing a certain number of creatures with Separatist weapons or pistols can grant you certain bonuses。‖color:245,215,15,255‖the count is not reset upon death‖color:end‖
    When you kill creatures with ‖color:245,215,15,255‖Coalition‖color:end‖ weapons or ‖color:245,215,15,255‖pistols‖color:end‖:
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖25‖color:end‖ creatures reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖10% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using Coalition weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖50‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖5% weapon damage‖color:end‖ when using Coalition weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖75‖color:end‖ creatures reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖15% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using Coalition weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖100‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖8% weapon damage‖color:end‖ when using Coalition weapons.
  </talentdescription.tsm_gunskill_mastery_lm>
  <talentname.tsm_gunskill_mastery_fkj>Separatist Firearms Proficiency</talentname.tsm_gunskill_mastery_fkj>
  <talentdescription.tsm_gunskill_mastery_fkj>When you possess the talent, killing a certain number of creatures with Separatist weapons or Hand Cannon can grant you certain bonuses。‖color:245,215,15,255‖the count is not reset upon death‖color:end‖
    When you kill creatures with ‖color:245,215,15,255‖Separatist‖color:end‖ weapons or ‖color:245,215,15,255‖Hand Cannon‖color:end‖:
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖25‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖5% weapon damage‖color:end‖ when using Separatist weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖50‖color:end‖ creatures reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖20% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using Separatist weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖75‖color:end‖ creatures reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖10% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using Separatist weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖100‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖5% weapon damage‖color:end‖ when using Splinter weapons.
  </talentdescription.tsm_gunskill_mastery_fkj>
  <talentname.tsm_gunskill_mastery_tsm>TSM Firearms Proficiency</talentname.tsm_gunskill_mastery_tsm>
  <talentdescription.tsm_gunskill_mastery_tsm>When you possess the talent, killing a certain number of creatures with TSM weapons or SMG can grant you certain bonuses。‖color:245,215,15,255‖the count is not reset upon death‖color:end‖
    When you kill creatures with ‖color:245,215,15,255‖TSM‖color:end‖ weapons or ‖color:245,215,15,255‖SMG‖color:end‖:
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖50‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖6% weapon damage‖color:end‖ and reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖12% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using TSM weapons;
    Killing ‖color:0,150,0,255‖100‖color:end‖ creatures increases ‖color:0,150,0,255‖6% weapon damage‖color:end‖, reduces ‖color:0,150,0,255‖13% weapon spread‖color:end‖ when using TSM weapons.
  </talentdescription.tsm_gunskill_mastery_tsm>
  <!--伤害类型-->
  <afflictionname.tsm_ondeath>Dead Sea</afflictionname.tsm_ondeath>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_ondeath>What are you seeking?</afflictiondescription.tsm_ondeath>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_ondeath>What are you seeking?</afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_ondeath>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_ondeath>What are you seeking?</afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_ondeath>
  <afflictionname.tsm_fire_water>Boiling Sea</afflictionname.tsm_fire_water>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_fire_water>Hot! Hot! This waterway is extremely hot, it almost feels like an oven inside the submarine, the water outside is boiling\nDuring this round, players' maximum health is reduced by 30%\nContacting water will cause continuous burns, different diving suit depths take different burn damage</afflictiondescription.tsm_fire_water>
  <afflictionname.tsm_eyi_attack>Combat Evil Plague Normal State</afflictionname.tsm_eyi_attack>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_eyi_attack>The Evil Plague within you is in a stable state, continuously providing bonuses in combat.</afflictiondescription.tsm_eyi_attack>
  <afflictionname.tsm_stress_resistance>Strong Will</afflictionname.tsm_stress_resistance>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_stress_resistance>Your will is very firm at this moment, able to withstand the torment of other things on your mind.</afflictiondescription.tsm_stress_resistance>
  <afflictionname.tsm_stress>Mental Stress</afflictionname.tsm_stress>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_stress>You are currently feeling very tense and in pain.</afflictiondescription.tsm_stress>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_stress>Committed suicide.</afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_stress>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_stress>You committed suicide.</afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_stress>
  <afflictionname.tsm_eyi_provocative>Flesh Information Pheromone</afflictionname.tsm_eyi_provocative>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_eyi_provocative>You have been bitten by a rotting corpse; now the lacerations and bite wounds you receive will increase, and enemies will be more likely to target you.</afflictiondescription.tsm_eyi_provocative>
  <afflictionname.tsm_virusstage>Flesh Embryo</afflictionname.tsm_virusstage>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage>The Evil Plague virus is using your body as a breeding ground, forcibly altering the host's genes to match the Skin Breaker.</afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage>
  <afflictionname.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>Virus Dormant Stage</afflictionname.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory></afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage_inhibitory>
  <afflictionname.tsm_virusstage_deep>Evil Plague</afflictionname.tsm_virusstage_deep>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage_deep>The host's genes have been altered; this situation is basically irreversible, and the body is undergoing changes.</afflictiondescription.tsm_virusstage_deep>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_virusstage_deep>I swim upstream, you are like in the center of the water.</afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_virusstage_deep>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_virusstage_deep>I swim upstream, you are like in the center of the water.</afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_virusstage_deep>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_eyi_bite>Insect Bite</afflictionname.tsmmission_eyi_bite>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_bite>You have been bitten by an Evil Plague bloodworm.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_bite>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_monster_50>Broken Bones</afflictionname.tsmmission_monster_50>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_monster_50>You feel as if your bones have broken/n At this moment, the tearing and biting damage you suffer will increase.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_monster_50>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_ai_mod_resistancefor>T.S.M Sunset Stable Evil Plague State</afflictionname.tsmmission_ai_mod_resistancefor>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_ai_mod_resistancefor>Alters part of the DNA sequence to make the body reject foreign parasites.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_ai_mod_resistancefor>
  <afflictionname.tsmmission_bodyguard_resistancefor>TSM Bodyguard Enhancement</afflictionname.tsmmission_bodyguard_resistancefor>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_bodyguard_resistancefor></afflictiondescription.tsmmission_bodyguard_resistancefor>
  <afflictionname.tsm_eyi_stable_state>Stable Evil Plague Normal State</afflictionname.tsm_eyi_stable_state>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_0_1>At this stage, you will be immune to water pressure, require no oxygen, increase maximum health by 30%, and will no longer become addicted to drugs. Burns will recover quickly, and you will rapidly heal from Flesh Embryos and Husk Infection.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_0_1>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_1_4>At this stage, you will not need oxygen and will gain 30% swimming speed.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_1_4>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_4_8>At this stage, you will gain immunity to all toxins.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_4_8>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_8_16>At this stage, you will be immune to water pressure of 6213 meters and slowly heal from hypoxia.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_8_16>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_16_22>At this stage, you will quickly heal from bleeding and blood loss.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_16_22>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_22_28>At this stage, you will gain 30% physical damage resistance.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_22_28>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_28_33>At this stage, you will gain a 10% attack speed increase for ranged weapons and reduce spread by 20%.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_28_33>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_33_37>At this stage, you will gain 50% resistance to stuns and burns.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_33_37>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_37_39>At this stage, you will slowly heal physical damage and burns.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_37_39>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_39_42>At this stage, you will gain 50% resistance to Opioid poisoning, Withdrawal, Addiction, Alcohol poisoning, Psychosis, Husk Infection, as well as Acid Burns which will heal slowly.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_39_42>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_42_44>At this stage, you will gain 25% attack power, 50% melee strike force, and 10% turret attack speed.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_42_44>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_44_48>At this stage, you will have 55% bleeding resistance.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_44_48>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_48_55>At this stage, you will be immune to water pressure of 5112 meters.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_48_55>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_55_59>At this stage, all your skill levels will increase by 18, and repair speed will increase by 44%.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_55_59>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_59_63>At this stage, you will gain 30% melee attack speed, 20% movement speed, and 40% stun resistance.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_59_63>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_63_65>At this stage, you will gain 30% damage resistance and 30% maximum health.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_63_65>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_65_69>At this stage, you will gain the ability to slowly heal from all toxins.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_65_69>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_69_72>At this stage, you can recover from stun faster, increase attack power by 30% and ranged attack speed by 5%.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_69_72>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_72_76>At this stage, you will never die.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_72_76>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_76_83>At this stage, your item crafting speed will increase by 150%, and crafting level will increase by 2.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_76_83>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_83_85>At this stage, you will be immune to water pressure of 6177 meters and will not need oxygen.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_83_85>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_85_90>At this stage, you will gain 25% resistance to physical damage and burns, and gain 25% attack power.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_85_90>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_90_95>At this stage, all healing effects on you will increase by 100%.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_90_95>
  <afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_95_100>At this stage, part of your body's DNA sequence will change, beginning to reject foreign parasites.</afflictiondescription.tsmmission_eyi_95_100>
  <afflictionname.tsm_zs>irradiate</afflictionname.tsm_zs>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_zs>You've been exposed to some kind of radiation for so long, your skin starts to burn.</afflictiondescription.tsm_zs>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_zs>lethal exposure</afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_zs>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_zs>lethal exposure</afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_zs>
  <afflictionname.eyi_zb_eyivariant>Transformative Intrusion</afflictionname.eyi_zb_eyivariant>
  <afflictionname.triton_7L>Triton</afflictionname.triton_7L>
  <afflictiondescription.triton_7L>Wound acused by Triton_7L，presenting induced corruption.If not handled promptly, it may induce tritium poisoning, resulting in burns and other issues.</afflictiondescription.triton_7L>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.triton_7L>Your body and tissue has been seriously damaged because of the large amount of Tritium.</afflictioncauseofdeath.triton_7L>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.triton_7L>A large amount of Tritium stayed in your body,causing decay and putrefaction</afflictioncauseofdeathself.triton_7L>
  <afflictiondescription.triton_7L.low>It seems that the wound is not too bad for now, but there is a risk of deteriorate.</afflictiondescription.triton_7L.low>
  <afflictiondescription.triton_7L>The bullet penatrated your body，a strong feeling of burning comes from the wound，part of your body tissue has been pulled out from yourself.</afflictiondescription.triton_7L>
  <afflictionname.triton_9C>Tritium Poisoning</afflictionname.triton_9C>
  <afflictiondescription.triton_9C>The part that was hit began to rot, and you felt your stomach churning, with an urge to vomit.</afflictiondescription.triton_9C>
  <afflictiondescription.triton_9C.low.self>The wound began to feel like it was burning, as if it were on fire.</afflictiondescription.triton_9C.low.self>
  <afflictiondescription.triton_9C.high.self>You began to feel dizzy and vomit, with the wound decaying and becoming putrid.</afflictiondescription.triton_9C.high.self>
  <afflictiondescription.triton_9C.high>You couldn't stop vomiting, and they began to develop ulcers and various symptoms of soft tissue necrosis.</afflictiondescription.triton_9C.high>
  <afflictionname.triton_burn>Tritium Burning</afflictionname.triton_burn>
  <afflictiondescription.triton_burn>A burning sensation began to develop at the site of the wound.</afflictiondescription.triton_burn>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armorbreak_jz>Broken Armor</afflictionname.tsm_armorbreak_jz>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armorbreak_jz>Become easier to be penatrated by bullets.</afflictiondescription.tsm_armorbreak_jz>
  <entityname.triton_9C_antidote>Specialized wound decontaminant</entityname.triton_9C_antidote>
  <entitydescription.triton_9C_antidote>Medications for treating special injuries.</entitydescription.triton_9C_antidote>
  <afflictionname.zlyz>Gravity suppression</afflictionname.zlyz>
  <afflictiondescription.zlyz>You feel an intangible pressure that immobilizes you.</afflictiondescription.zlyz>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.zlyz>Heavy</afflictioncauseofdeath.zlyz>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.zlyz>Consequences for ignoring the rules</afflictioncauseofdeathself.zlyz>
  <afflictionname.zlqy>Gravitational traction</afflictionname.zlqy>
  <afflictiondescription.zlqy>Let's sink in the dark curtain made up of Kind and Evil.</afflictiondescription.zlqy>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.zlqy>Annihilation</afflictioncauseofdeath.zlqy>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.zlqy>The knell has already tolled.</afflictioncauseofdeathself.zlqy>
  <afflictionname.tsm_bl>Burst</afflictionname.tsm_bl>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_bl>When a bullet hits the human body and explodes, the fragments and the pressure generated can cause direct and severe damage to the body. It seems that if these wounds are not properly treated, the effectiveness of treating other injuries will be significantly reduced.</afflictiondescription.tsm_bl>
  <afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_bl>Your body has burst out.</afflictioncauseofdeath.tsm_bl>
  <afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_bl>Killed by high-explosive rounds</afflictioncauseofdeathself.tsm_bl>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_bl.low>Some small fragments entered your body after the bullet exploded. It seems that if these wounds are not properly treated, the effectiveness of treating other injuries will be significantly reduced.</afflictiondescription.tsm_bl.low>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_bl>The high-explosive round destroyed some of your body tissue, with fragments and blast pressure wreaking havoc inside you.</afflictiondescription.tsm_bl>
  <afflictionname.tsm_aftermath_success>Quality battlefield medical treatment</afflictionname.tsm_aftermath_success>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_aftermath_success>The injured area was well treated and bandaged, but it still affected your mobility and weapon use, making movement inconvenient.\n-50% of rapairspeed\n-30% of weaponsSkill\n-20% of movementspeed</afflictiondescription.tsm_aftermath_success>
  <afflictionname.tsm_aftermath_failure>Inadequate battlefield medical treatment</afflictionname.tsm_aftermath_failure>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_aftermath_failure>The doctor only ensured that you wouldn't die on the front line. The wounds were poorly treated, and you could move temporarily, but every movement caused pain throughout your body.\n-70% of repairspeed\n-50 of weaponsSkill\n-15 of medicalskill\nnow you can only walk</afflictiondescription.tsm_aftermath_failure>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_allbuff>Full protection plate</afflictionname.tsm_armor_allbuff>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_allbuff>Protection against multiple types of injuries</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_allbuff>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_bleeding>Bleeding Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_bleeding>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_bleeding>Protction type：Bleeding</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_bleeding>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_lacerations>Lacerations Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_lacerations>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_lacerations>Protction type：Lacerations</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_lacerations>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_stun>Stun Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_stun>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_stun>Protction type：Stun</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_stun>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_blunttrauma>Blunttrauma Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_blunttrauma>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_blunttrauma>Protction type：Blunttrauma</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_blunttrauma>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_huskinfection>Huskinfection Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_huskinfection>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_huskinfection>Protction type：Huskinfection</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_huskinfection>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_paralysis>Paralysis Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_paralysis>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_paralysis>Protction type：Paralysis</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_paralysis>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_triton>Special injuries Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_triton>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_triton>Protction type：Tritium Poisoning、Burst</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_triton>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_bitewounds>Bite Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_bitewounds>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_bitewounds>Protction type：Bitewounds</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_bitewounds>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_explosiondamage>Explosion Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_explosiondamage>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_explosiondamage>Protction type：Explosiondamage</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_explosiondamage>
  <afflictionname.tsm_armor_gunshotwound>Gunshot Protction</afflictionname.tsm_armor_gunshotwound>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_gunshotwound>Protction type：Gunshot</afflictiondescription.tsm_armor_gunshotwound>
  <afflictionname.tsm_kep_buff>"San ShenQiu"Auxiliary system</afflictionname.tsm_kep_buff>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_kep_buff>When you wear two pieces of the San ShenQiu set, you gain a 20% damage boost, 10% attack-speed increase, 20% stun resistance and reduce 12% of maximum health. Equipping all three pieces will give you immunity to water pressure and thermal-vision functions.</afflictiondescription.tsm_kep_buff>
  <afflictionname.tsm_anger>Anger</afflictionname.tsm_anger>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_anger>Experimental injection\n\nDevelopment site：The JiuZhou Reaserch Site\n\nEnhancement Type：\n20% of movementspeed in Land/Water\n20% of maximum health\n20% of meleeattackspeed\n15% of meleeattackdamage\n\nAccess Level：Ⅱ</afflictiondescription.tsm_anger>
  <afflictionname.tsm_68_51>6.8*51 Mark</afflictionname.tsm_68_51>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_68_51></afflictiondescription.tsm_68_51>
  <afflictionname.tsm_teargas_debuff>tear gas</afflictionname.tsm_teargas_debuff>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_teargas_debuff>After inhaling an excessive amount of tear gas, you will first experience severe coughing accompanied by a feeling of suffocation. This will then cause your body to be unable to move at full speed, and at the same time, the stability of your hands will be affected, making it impossible to aim accurately.</afflictiondescription.tsm_teargas_debuff>
  <afflictionname.tsm_burneyes_debuff>visual disruption</afflictionname.tsm_burneyes_debuff>
  <afflictiondescription.tsm_burneyes_debuff>Overusing the telescope amplified by the radio booster pack will blur your vision, leaving you unable to see clearly. This effect will fade gradually.</afflictiondescription.tsm_burneyes_debuff>

  <!--站点-->
  <locationdescription.tsm_city>The largest city under T.S.M, bustling with people, with comprehensive facilities and services.</locationdescription.tsm_city>
  <locationname.tsm_city>TSM Fortress City</locationname.tsm_city>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_city>[name]</locationnameformat.tsm_city>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_city>[name] City</locationnameformat.tsm_city>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_city>[name] Station</locationnameformat.tsm_city>
  <locationname.tsm_mine>TSM Mining Station</locationname.tsm_mine>
  <locationdescription.tsm_mine>A mineral mining site under T.S.M, where you can go deep into the mines to mine.</locationdescription.tsm_mine>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_mine>[name]</locationnameformat.tsm_mine>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_mine>[name] City</locationnameformat.tsm_mine>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_mine>[name] Station</locationnameformat.tsm_mine>
  <locationname.tsm_military>TSM Armed Division</locationname.tsm_military>
  <locationdescription.tsm_military>A military stronghold under T.S.M.</locationdescription.tsm_military>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_military>[name]</locationnameformat.tsm_military>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_military>[name] City</locationnameformat.tsm_military>
  <locationnameformat.tsm_military>[name] Station</locationnameformat.tsm_military>
  <locationname.tsm_city.0>Huaishuo</locationname.tsm_city.0>
  <locationname.tsm_city.1>Yong'an</locationname.tsm_city.1>
  <locationname.tsm_city.2>Fuming</locationname.tsm_city.2>
  <locationname.tsm_city.3>Chang'an</locationname.tsm_city.3>
  <locationname.tsm_city.4>Yingcui</locationname.tsm_city.4>
  <locationname.tsm_city.5>Puji</locationname.tsm_city.5>
  <locationname.tsm_city.6>New Shanghai</locationname.tsm_city.6>
  <locationname.tsm_city.7>New Chengdu</locationname.tsm_city.7>
  <locationname.tsm_city.8>Polaris</locationname.tsm_city.8>

  <locationname.tsm_military.0>Hailing Port</locationname.tsm_military.0>
  <locationname.tsm_military.1>Mahogany Garrison</locationname.tsm_military.1>
  <locationname.tsm_military.2>Black Sea Garrison</locationname.tsm_military.2>
  <locationname.tsm_military.3>Wohen Mountain</locationname.tsm_military.3>
  <locationname.tsm_military.4>Aizu</locationname.tsm_military.4>
  <locationname.tsm_military.5>Minggang</locationname.tsm_military.5>
  <locationname.tsm_military.6>Paldiski</locationname.tsm_military.6>
  <locationname.tsm_military.7>Belgrade</locationname.tsm_military.7>
  <locationname.tsm_military.8>Zhenyuan</locationname.tsm_military.8>
  <locationname.tsm_military.9>Wuchuan</locationname.tsm_military.9>
  <locationname.tsm_military.10>Huaihuang</locationname.tsm_military.10>
  <locationname.tsm_military.11>Wu'an</locationname.tsm_military.11>
  <locationname.tsm_military.12>Sea Wall</locationname.tsm_military.12>
  <locationname.tsm_military.13>Zhenjiuming</locationname.tsm_military.13>
  <locationname.tsm_military.14>Yuzhang</locationname.tsm_military.14>
  <locationname.tsm_military.15>Wupan</locationname.tsm_military.15>

  <locationname.tsm_mine.0>Renofar</locationname.tsm_mine.0>
  <locationname.tsm_mine.1>Fanoi</locationname.tsm_mine.1>
  <locationname.tsm_mine.2>Gnandin</locationname.tsm_mine.2>
  <locationname.tsm_mine.3>Sacred Grove</locationname.tsm_mine.3>
  <locationname.tsm_mine.4>Shark Station</locationname.tsm_mine.4>
  <locationname.tsm_mine.5>Qianjun Mountain</locationname.tsm_mine.5>
  <locationname.tsm_mine.6>Shenming</locationname.tsm_mine.6>
  <locationname.tsm_mine.7>Shenyue</locationname.tsm_mine.7>
  <locationname.tsm_mine.8>Yishan</locationname.tsm_mine.8>

  <!--标识-->
  <semi_auto>Semi-auto</semi_auto>
  <fullauto>Fullauto</fullauto>
  <burst>Burst</burst>
  <burst>Burst</burst>
  <nightvision>Activate the night vision</nightvision>
  <thermalgoggles>Activate the thermal goggles.</thermalgoggles>
  <tsm_mode>Fire mode switch toggle</tsm_mode>
  <laser>Laser pointer</laser>
  <pucsscooter>Propulsion system</pucsscooter>
  <lightswitch>Fulllight system</lightswitch>
  <mode.laser>Cutting mode</mode.laser>
  <mode.charge>Charging mode</mode.charge>
  <activate>For XXX,Use self-detonation on me!</activate>
  <fixproblem>Clearing button\nShit, this thing uses like a wooden stick, run!</fixproblem>
  <minus1seconds>Minus 1 sec</minus1seconds>
  <plus1seconds>Add 1 sec</plus1seconds>
  <bomb.timer>Set the timer</bomb.timer>
  <tsm_boom>Press to start a 10-second countdown.</tsm_boom>
  <subcategory.TSM>T.S.M will secure you safety\nA hero is not judged solely by success or failure.</subcategory.TSM>
  <subcategory.the_adventists>The adventists</subcategory.the_adventists>
  <subcategory.tsm_separatists>Separatists</subcategory.tsm_separatists>
  <subcategory.tsm_coalition>Coalition</subcategory.tsm_coalition>
  <displayname.防护服改造>[itemname] (Protective suit modification)</displayname.防护服改造>
  <tos>Turn off the sensor.</tos>
  <dm>Disarm the land mine</dm>
  <entityname.tsm_collider_head>Unpenetrated</entityname.tsm_collider_head>
  <tsm_on>Enable the function</tsm_on>
  <tsm_gun_up>overhead shooting</tsm_gun_up>
  <renou>Test Dummy</renou>
  <takeit>take out ammunition</takeit>
  <!--msg-->
  <itemmsgreactorfuelrequired>Fuel Rod Required</itemmsgreactorfuelrequired>
  <!--加载界面-->
  <loadingscreentip>Crystallography can mainly be purchased at sites with a difficulty level of 36 or above. Of course, they might also be found in ruins-TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>Stellar Humbly can only be sold by merchants in cities or research institutes with a difficulty level of 40 or above. If you are lucky enough, you can also find them in ruins or shipwrecks—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>Some parts of the War Chariot and the Flying Crow can be bought at various sites, but the main body of the gun has been lost. Perhaps it can be found in shipwrecks?—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>ARS is a company that makes products with an automatic recording function, but behind the scenes, they are collecting various materials for trade or to strengthen their internal military forces—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>There are reports that the Adventists are setting up "beacons" at various abandoned sites—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>TSM originally started in the Source of the Lightless Sea—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>The Coalition and the separatists are engaged in a war—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>As the war intensifies, TSM's board of directors has announced that the income from the escort service project has exceeded other service projects for the first time and is considering increasing investment—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>After a long period of construction, the Ice city project has finally been completed. It is reported that it will be opened to the public for residential and commercial services after all project inspections are successful—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>DS104 border site has lost contact: TSM has dispatched relevant personnel to investigate—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>TSM has three armed departments: the Advanced Combat Division, the Dusk Mountain Combat Division, and the Jiuzhou Combat Division. Their functions correspond to combat against humans, corporate security, and combat against monsters, respectively—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>TSM is still just a company, but it also plays a key role in the development of Europa, urban construction, and technological research and development. Its subordinate departments cover almost all industries on Europa, such as military manufacturing, medical manufacturing, schools, and docks, and even have their own widow sites—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>After the Adventists demonstrated the "miracle," their followers increased exponentially, including powerful individuals such as high-ranking officials from the Coalition—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>The Adventists' mission is to bring their unique god to Europa, but the god's arrival requires a vessel. Currently, no living beings on Europa are suitable for this role, so their goal now is to create a perfect being—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>The separatists are a more threatening and powerful group that has broken away from the separatist organization, intending to overthrow the Coalition's iron-fisted rule—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>Communication has developed significantly, but there are still limitations—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>Whether it is the Coalition, separatists, or TSM forces, they will call for reinforcements after encountering their first enemy. Be sure to be cautious.—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>The Beowulf Squadron is the Coalition's most elite riot control and counter-terrorism unit. As the war continues to escalate, the responsibilities of this unit have far exceeded traditional riot control tasks and have been granted higher authority. Now, they are not only the pacifiers on the battlefield but also play the roles of judges, police, and executioners, becoming the Coalition's truly authoritative force that integrates trial and execution.—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>The occupying forces are the Coalition's ace troops, known for their powerful heavy firepower, comprehensive support capabilities, and thick armor. They are the most formidable force on the conventional battlefield, showing overwhelming combat effectiveness in both offense and defense.—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>EMBI, short for Europa Magic Biotechnology Company, mainly develops biological weapons—TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>Press Alt + F for quick activation of overhead shooting.    Press Alt + G for quick activation of helmet function.--------TSM</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>The Thunder and The Inferno could directly damage targets within submarines, challenging the EMBI proving grounds or the Triplet without preparation is suicide! Try to lead the targets away with flares, to buy time for repair or damage------suger security officer biology lecture-9</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>The Thunder and The Inferno could directly damage targets within submarines, challenging the EMBI proving grounds or the Triplet without preparation is suicide! Try to lead the targets away with flares, to buy time for repair or damage------suger security officer biology lecture-9</loadingscreentip>
</infotexts>